<DTO_Category xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/NetFlix.Models"><Id>1</Id><Name>Action &amp; Adventure</Name><Titles><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A taxi driver, a gangster and an athlete struggle to better their lives despite obstacles like crooked politicians, evil dons and caste barriers.</Description><Id>81018234</Id><Name>?Goli Soda 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Fierce mammoth hunter D'Leh sets out on an impossible journey to rescue the woman he loves from a vicious warlord and save the people of his village.</Description><Id>70060018</Id><Name>10,000 B.C.</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In the age of the Ming Dynasty, Quinglong is the best of the Jinyiwei, an elite assassin squad made up of highly trained former street urchins. When evil eunuch Jia unseats the emperor, Quinglong is called to action but is quickly betrayed.</Description><Id>70130142</Id><Name>14 Blades</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Tasked with escorting a prosecution witness to court, an aging cop gears up for the 16-block trek – but they'll be lucky to make it there alive.</Description><Id>70044870</Id><Name>16 Blocks</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In the frozen tundra of a futuristic Arizona where humans have been forced underground, a soldier hunts the bioengineered leader of a rebellion.</Description><Id>80184973</Id><Name>2307: Winter's Dream</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Revived by an experimental procedure, a hit man gets to live an extra 24 hours – which he uses to avenge his dead wife and child and redeem himself.</Description><Id>80208951</Id><Name>24 Hours to Live</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Four brothers learn that they have inherited ancestral land, but must fight to claim it when a greedy feudal lord threatens to take it over.</Description><Id>80137461</Id><Name>25 Kille</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a musician dies under suspicious circumstances, a hard-drinking detective and a music fan investigate why rock stars often die at the age of 27.</Description><Id>80241044</Id><Name>27, el club de los malditos</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Yanto asks his friends to help save a girlfriend who was kidnapped by a mobster. Silly slapstick and campy crimefighting ensues.</Description><Id>81037984</Id><Name>5 Cowok Jagoan</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When armed gunmen seize the Iranian Embassy in 1980, a tense six-day standoff ensues while elite British soldiers prepare for a dangerous raid.</Description><Id>80178280</Id><Name>6 Days</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After faking his death, a tech billionaire recruits a team of international operatives for a bold and bloody mission to take down a brutal dictator.</Description><Id>81001887</Id><Name>6 Underground</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a postapocalyptic world, rag-doll robots hide in fear from dangerous machines out to exterminate them, until a brave newcomer joins the group.</Description><Id>70113538</Id><Name>9</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A timid man gets unexpected superpowers while trying to save his family's land and a sacred tree from a ruthless tycoon.</Description><Id>80136925</Id><Name>A Flying Jatt</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After receiving an anonymous tip about a bomb, a police commissioner must negotiate with the terrorist, who demands the release of four militants.</Description><Id>70107499</Id><Name>A Wednesday</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Young motocross racer Miles Hill helps a top-secret robotic combat dog evade its ruthless creator and the military, who are in hot pursuit.</Description><Id>80195967</Id><Name>A.X.L.</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An intrepid police inspector forced into a desk job must take matters into his own hands when ruthless criminals are released on a technicality.</Description><Id>20254278</Id><Name>Aakhri Adaalat</Name><ReleaseYear>1988</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Following the mysterious death of his parents, a young man finds himself enmeshed in the dark world of drugs and crime.</Description><Id>81035861</Id><Name>Abdo Mota</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two Turkish agents are sent to New York City on a mission to capture a notorious terrorist known only as "Dejjal" (Arabic for Antichrist).</Description><Id>70233894</Id><Name>Act of Vengeance</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Devastated by the murder of his wife and child, a formerly fast-talking lawyer takes a vow of silence and trains himself for a mission of revenge.</Description><Id>80190283</Id><Name>Acts of Vengeance</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Aiming to hasten an uprising, the leader of an underground rebellion dispatches acrobatic assassin Aeon Flux to eliminate the government's top leader.</Description><Id>70045919</Id><Name>Æon Flux</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An American tourist and his friends are partying in Chile, but a major earthquake devastates the area and forces them to scramble for survival.</Description><Id>70260374</Id><Name>Aftershock</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his protégé goes rogue and poses a grave threat to the government he serves, a veteran officer of the Indian Army tries to stop him at all costs.</Description><Id>80243408</Id><Name>Aiyaary</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A garden gnome vendor and his brother-in-law attend a trade fair in Sofia, where they accidentally stumble into shenanigans involving a mafia boss.</Description><Id>80231064</Id><Name>Ali Baba ve 7 Cüceler</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A simple village man is thrown into a web of political intrigue after he takes on a powerful and ruthless gang of bandits.</Description><Id>80158543</Id><Name>Alibaba Aur 40 Chor</Name><ReleaseYear>1980</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The U.S. Navy Seal team tackles a top-secret mission at a research center where scientists have mysteriously disappeared and another life form awaits.</Description><Id>80232502</Id><Name>Alien Warfare</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A battle-scarred Special Ops military vet joins a CIA-funded assignment to take down a Russian terrorist and his trigger-happy comrades.</Description><Id>80220311</Id><Name>All the Devil's Men</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Abandoned in a park by their father, Amar, Akbar and Anthony grow up independently and have no knowledge of one another. They're reunited as adults when, by coincidence, they all give blood at the same hospital.</Description><Id>247747</Id><Name>Amar Akbar Anthony</Name><ReleaseYear>1977</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An ex-con is just getting his life back on track when his older brother is released from prison and drags him into the underworld for one final heist.</Description><Id>80017261</Id><Name>American Heist</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After growing up amidst the gang wars of his hometown, Vincent forms an entrepreneurial squad of his own and ends up on the wrong side of the law.</Description><Id>80182447</Id><Name>Angamaly Diaries</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An unlucky, debt-ridden teen resorts to his math skills when he's forced into a deadly tournament of rock-paper-scissors run by a diabolical host.</Description><Id>81004470</Id><Name>Animal World</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Mild-mannered Krishna comes to Mumbai to search for his gang-leader brother, and quickly finds himself in way over his head.</Description><Id>80190101</Id><Name>Anjaan</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A tough-as-nails treasure hunter protects a humanitarian doctor as she tries to cure a supernatural disease caused by a mysterious witch.</Description><Id>81060043</Id><Name>Antidote</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Problems big and small pop up when Scott Lang, aka Ant-Man, gets drafted by Dr. Hank Pym and Hope van Dyne, aka the Wasp, for an urgent rescue mission.</Description><Id>80220813</Id><Name>Ant-Man and the Wasp</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After the world's top scientists disappear, orphaned April secretly forges ahead with a family experiment and gets tangled up in a vast conspiracy.</Description><Id>80062096</Id><Name>April and the Extraordinary World</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A futuristic France tries to keep its people from despair and rebellion over crippling poverty by engaging them with a violent TV competition show.</Description><Id>80165083</Id><Name>Arès</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This animated retelling of the classic Indian tale of Prince Arjun – part of the Sanskrit epic Mahabharata – begins during the prince's youth.</Description><Id>70139073</Id><Name>Arjun: The Warrior Prince</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This elaborate Bollywood epic dramatizes one man's transformation from a vengeful and cunning warrior into a legendary leader and teacher of Buddhism.</Description><Id>60021758</Id><Name>Asoka</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Caught between a corrupt mayor and a prosecutor intent on exposing political depravity, a police detective must decide whose side he's on.</Description><Id>80144372</Id><Name>Asura: The City of Madness</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The world's most shagadelic spy continues his fight against the diabolical Dr. Evil, who's teamed with a new foe: 1970s villain Goldmember.</Description><Id>60023608</Id><Name>Austin Powers in Goldmember</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When diabolical genius Dr. Evil travels back in time to steal superspy Austin Powers's "mojo," Austin must return to the swingin' '60s himself.</Description><Id>21302357</Id><Name>Austin Powers: The Spy Who Shagged Me</Name><ReleaseYear>1999</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Betrayed by his loan shark brother, a hardened convict escapes from prison while on furlough to exact revenge against the people who made him a killer.</Description><Id>80991316</Id><Name>Avengement</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Superheroes amass to stop intergalactic sociopath Thanos from acquiring a full set of Infinity Stones and wiping out half of all life in the universe.</Description><Id>80219127</Id><Name>Avengers: Infinity War</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In 1975, during the government-declared Emergency, thief Bhawani and his crew plan a daring robbery to reclaim his royal lover's seized treasures.</Description><Id>80211134</Id><Name>Baadshaho</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A martial artist faces his biggest test when he has to travel to Bangkok to rescue the woman he loves from the clutches of his romantic rival.</Description><Id>80104648</Id><Name>Baaghi</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To avenge his father's death, a young man leads an army into battle against a cruel tyrant in this Hindi conclusion to the historic saga.</Description><Id>80203996</Id><Name>Baahubali 2: The Conclusion (Hindi Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To avenge his father's death, a young man leads an army into battle against a cruel tyrant in this Malayalam conclusion to the historic saga.</Description><Id>80203998</Id><Name>Baahubali 2: The Conclusion (Malayalam Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To avenge his father's death, a young man leads an army into battle against a cruel tyrant in this Tamil conclusion to the historic saga.</Description><Id>80203997</Id><Name>Baahubali 2: The Conclusion (Tamil Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Villagers in the kingdom of Mahismati rescue a baby who is destined to embark on a heroic quest in this English version of S.S. Rajamouli's epic.</Description><Id>80205231</Id><Name>Baahubali: The Beginning (English Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Villagers in the kingdom of Mahismati rescue a baby who is destined to embark on a heroic quest in this Hindi version of S.S. Rajamouli's epic.</Description><Id>80204117</Id><Name>Baahubali: The Beginning (Hindi Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Villagers in the kingdom of Mahismati rescue a baby who is destined to embark on a heroic quest in this Malayalam version of S.S. Rajamouli's epic.</Description><Id>80204119</Id><Name>Baahubali: The Beginning (Malayalam Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Villagers in the kingdom of Mahismati rescue a baby who is destined to embark on a heroic quest in this Tamil version of S.S. Rajamouli's epic.</Description><Id>80204118</Id><Name>Baahubali: The Beginning (Tamil Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this sequel to the 1991 film, a determined fire investigator recruits an imprisoned arsonist to help untangle a web of fire, murder and corruption.</Description><Id>81053958</Id><Name>Backdraft 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this fast-paced actioner, two Miami narcotics cops are hot on the trail of a master crook who has snatched $100 million worth of heroin.</Description><Id>269880</Id><Name>Bad Boys</Name><ReleaseYear>1995</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this hyperkinetic sequel, a pair of Miami narcotics cops investigate a Cuban drug kingpin's connection to Florida's influx of Ecstasy.</Description><Id>60029167</Id><Name>Bad Boys II</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Recast as modern-day men, Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn draft their misfit cronies to help find the buried treasure the two have sought since boyhood.</Description><Id>80064273</Id><Name>Band of Robbers</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Heirless Maharaj Brajbhan leaves his throne to his cousin Vikram, but when Brajbhan's wife, Badi Rani, finally conceives, Vikram plots to destroy her.</Description><Id>80158388</Id><Name>Bandie</Name><ReleaseYear>1978</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A small but fierce group of resistance fighters engages in a brutal battle to protect their village from an army of Burmese invaders.</Description><Id>80007777</Id><Name>Bang Rajan 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A girl raised to be a government assassin just wants to be a normal teen – so she runs away and pretends to be a high school exchange student.</Description><Id>80049177</Id><Name>Barely Lethal</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A naïve young man and a rich city girl fall in love. Her stepfather, however, doesn't approve of the match and will stop at nothing to split the pair.</Description><Id>284890</Id><Name>Barsaat</Name><ReleaseYear>1995</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A team of mercenaries working with the CIA accepts an off-the-books mission in Chernobyl, where deadly human-controlled droids prepare an ambush.</Description><Id>80232404</Id><Name>Battle Drone</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A cooly confident aging hit man returns from exile in Paris to his old city, Mumbai, to revisit his past and perform one last job.</Description><Id>70204288</Id><Name>Bbuddah Hoga Terra Baap</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Finding himself in a desperate situation, undercover agent Emman asks his former best friend, Erika, to join him on a dangerous mission.</Description><Id>80094723</Id><Name>Beauty and the Bestie</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Loner Guts is recruited by Griffith and his band of mercenaries, but their ensuing success as a full-fledged army could lead to a horrible fate.</Description><Id>70258995</Id><Name>Berserk: The Golden Age Arc I - The Egg of the King</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>For three years, Guts believed his mission was to pursue Griffith's dream together with him. But in order to become Griffith's equal and truly be called his friend, Guts realizes he will have to leave the Band of the Hawk.</Description><Id>70276596</Id><Name>Berserk: The Golden Age Arc II - The Battle for Doldrey</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A year after he left the Band of the Hawk, Guts rejoins them in an epic battle to vanquish the God Hand and save Griffith from a hellish fate.</Description><Id>80063025</Id><Name>Berserk: The Golden Age Arc III - The Advent</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In the wake of an extraterrestrial invasion, a suspended L.A. cop teams up with survivors to stop the onslaught and rescue human captives.</Description><Id>80189853</Id><Name>Beyond Skyline</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A tenderfoot and two gamblers seeking their fortunes in a boom town instead find themselves defending it from a gunslinging preacher and his gang.</Description><Id>81001090</Id><Name>Big Kill</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A Istanbul mobster falls for an Indian yoga instructor whose abduction takes him on a wild rescue mission to Mumbai.</Description><Id>80227115</Id><Name>Bir Baba Hindu</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A unconventional, efficient Interpol special agent goes rogue and assembles a team of thieves to catch a shadowy hacker called "The Ghost."</Description><Id>80203776</Id><Name>Bitcoin Heist</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When U.S. forces attempt to capture two underlings of a Somali warlord, their helicopters are shot down and the Americans suffer heavy casualties.</Description><Id>60022056</Id><Name>Black Hawk Down</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>T'Challa, the superpowered new leader of the hidden, highly advanced African nation of Wakanda, strives to protect his home from enemies old and new.</Description><Id>80201906</Id><Name>Black Panther</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a number of Russian women are brutally murdered in Los Angeles, the police call on a Moscow detective to help track down the serial killer.</Description><Id>80164164</Id><Name>Black Rose</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A hard-driving submarine captain is hired to steal gold from a sunken Nazi sub, but there's no honor among thieves during this underwater heist.</Description><Id>80013271</Id><Name>Black Sea</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After discovering that their secret military prison is under attack by terrorists, a ragtag group of inmates does their best to neutralize the enemy.</Description><Id>80128691</Id><Name>Black Site Delta</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Inside a vast, self-replicating city bent on eliminating all life, mysterious loner Killy emerges to guide a remnant of humanity desperate to survive.</Description><Id>80115466</Id><Name>BLAME!</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When high schooler Ichigo is suddenly given reaper abilities, he really wants to give the powers back. But he'll have to reap some souls first.</Description><Id>80217733</Id><Name>Bleach</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his mind is fogged by a scimitar-weilding stranger, Mayuri destroys his laboratory, unleashing a cloud of reishi that lays waste to the Seiretei.</Description><Id>70208801</Id><Name>Bleach The Movie: Fade to Black</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a group of vicious Sinners plots to escape from this eternal prison in Hell, they discover that Substitute Soul Reaper Ichigo is the key to their freedom. The Sinners launch an attack and in the process kidnap Ichigo's younger sister.</Description><Id>70260383</Id><Name>Bleach the Movie: Hell Verse</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a cop loses his vision, his detecting skills stay sharp. Luckily, a rookie officer recognizes his extraordinary powers of deduction.</Description><Id>70285697</Id><Name>Blind Detective</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Caught between family pressures and small-time crime-fighting, a pair of bumbling cops tries to bust a massive drug deal and go down in history.</Description><Id>81228864</Id><Name>Blitz Patrollie</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Three friends on a wilderness trip find bags full of cash and must evade the criminal who hid the money in the first place.</Description><Id>80209153</Id><Name>Blood Money</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two veteran buddy cops are back for a second chapter, this time to tackle a car theft ring that turns out to be much more than they bargained for.</Description><Id>80131563</Id><Name>Bon Cop Bad Cop 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An English-speaking officer from Toronto and a French-speaking cop from Montreal are forced to work together to solve a crime.</Description><Id>70095265</Id><Name>Bon Cop, Bad Cop</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Following a fashion show mishap, three supermodels find themselves on the run from dangerous gangsters trying to recover a fortune in stolen diamonds.</Description><Id>60036746</Id><Name>Boom</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Disowned by his father as a boy, Surya is taken in by a crime boss. When his brother Shiv is wrongly imprisoned, his father pleads for Surya's help.</Description><Id>70295762</Id><Name>Boss</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The fourth film in the action franchise finds Boyka taking on brutal gangsters to protect the widow of a man he unintentionally killed in the ring.</Description><Id>80124099</Id><Name>Boyka: Undisputed</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In an LA rife with interspecies tensions, a human cop and his orc partner stumble on a powerful object and become embroiled in a prophesied turf war.</Description><Id>80119234</Id><Name>Bright</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While tracking down a seditious painter, an imperial guard is accused of a royal assassination attempt and framed in a complicated conspiracy.</Description><Id>80226242</Id><Name>Brotherhood of Blades II: The Infernal Battlefield</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two Indonesian brothers learn the ways of the American cowboy before returning home to avenge the murder of their father.</Description><Id>81019144</Id><Name>Buffalo Boys</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A special agent abruptly reunites with a criminal – once a former friend – when he attempts to use his identity to infiltrate and take down a cartel.</Description><Id>81214114</Id><Name>Bulletproof 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2020</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his son's mom runs afoul of Paris's criminal underworld, a thrill-seeking superbike racer begins moonlighting as a drug courier to clear her debt.</Description><Id>80171678</Id><Name>Burn Out</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When their diverse neighborhood is besieged by a mysterious militia, a grad student and an ex-Marine become an unlikely team in a battle for survival.</Description><Id>80174220</Id><Name>Bushwick</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a mazelike Manila slum, at war with incensed civilians and a brutal cartel, special agent Nina Manigan must fight her way through one fierce night.</Description><Id>80222787</Id><Name>BuyBust</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To blow off some steam, friends Akshay, Joshi and Lambodar, posing as a gang called C Kkompany, make a phony extortion demand to Joshi's apathetic son. The trio is shocked when their prank call makes them anonymous celebrities.</Description><Id>70109249</Id><Name>C Kkompany</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When Japanese troops invade Hong Kong, young Benny Ho flees to Macau and rises to the top of the city's casino business with pluck, diligence and wit.</Description><Id>70033643</Id><Name>Casino Tycoon</Name><ReleaseYear>1992</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Casino mogul Benny Ho wields enormous power. But a feud with his former partner and a massive fraud scheme soon threaten his family and his empire.</Description><Id>70033644</Id><Name>Casino Tycoon 2</Name><ReleaseYear>1992</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Torn between old camaraderie and recent tensions, three ex-soldiers reunite to explore a deadly cave but soon discover terror beyond all expectations.</Description><Id>80164206</Id><Name>Cave</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a futuristic society where a robot police force keeps crime at bay, a lone droid gains the power of artificial intelligence.</Description><Id>80016588</Id><Name>Chappie</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Three beauties use their looks, charm and martial-arts training to kick butt on the trail of stolen software in this reboot of the classic TV series.</Description><Id>60003242</Id><Name>Charlie's Angels</Name><ReleaseYear>2000</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this reboot of the TV classic, the Angels are tasked with finding lost rings encoded with the personal information of people in witness protection.</Description><Id>60027726</Id><Name>Charlie's Angels: Full Throttle</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In corrupt, British-colonized Hong Kong, a mainland Chinese immigrant rises to the top of the city's drug underworld with the help of a notorious cop.</Description><Id>80215782</Id><Name>Chasing the Dragon</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>What could have been a sad journey turns joyful for Rahul when he falls in love with a woman en route to submerging his grandfather's ashes.</Description><Id>70254350</Id><Name>Chennai Express</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A Chinese engineer travels to a war-torn African country to rebuild its telecommunications but instead finds massive corruption and explosive danger.</Description><Id>80992496</Id><Name>China Salesman</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young man in Kerala has two weeks to stop the woman he loves from a fixed marriage in the U.S., but he doesn't have the papers to get there.</Description><Id>80192548</Id><Name>CIA: Comrade in America</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When Darren Shan is taken to a circus that's chock-full of sideshow oddities, he meets a vampire and receives a life-changing bite on the neck.</Description><Id>70114022</Id><Name>Cirque du Freak: The Vampire's Assistant</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>If he is to save the life of the beautiful Princess Andromeda, the valiant Perseus must battle a host of powerful, beastly enemies.</Description><Id>70119812</Id><Name>Clash of the Titans</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A stylin' special agent chases down drug lords and does her part to stop trafficking. Soon, she finds herself seeking revenge on a dealer.</Description><Id>382650</Id><Name>Cleopatra Jones</Name><ReleaseYear>1973</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When attackers target the heiress she's protecting, battle-hardened bodyguard Sam scrambles to save her client – and teach her how to fight back.</Description><Id>80207371</Id><Name>Close</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this star-studded drama, six seemingly disparate stories explore the complicated links that humanity shares through the generations.</Description><Id>70248183</Id><Name>Cloud Atlas</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A going-away party in Manhattan is interrupted when a mysterious monster of epic proportions launches an attack on New York City.</Description><Id>70082268</Id><Name>Cloverfield</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A mild-mannered janitor duped into believing he's an undercover agent stumbles into an international arms ring plot involving the CIA and the FBI.</Description><Id>70044705</Id><Name>Code Name: The Cleaner</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Following a misunderstanding, a gangster and his boss part ways and become bitter enemies – with devastating consequences.</Description><Id>60036613</Id><Name>Company</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this remake of "Cellular," a debt collector becomes embroiled in intrigue after answering a random phone call from a stranger begging for help.</Description><Id>70118801</Id><Name>Connected</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Following the death of his wife and daughter in a terrorist attack, an ex-Indian army commando agrees to infiltrate a terrorist cell.</Description><Id>70105459</Id><Name>Contract</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young woman in ancient China longs for an adventurous life rather than a dull arranged marriage in Ang Lee's Oscar-winning martial arts epic.</Description><Id>60002907</Id><Name>Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon</Name><ReleaseYear>2000</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Renowned warrior Yu Shu-Lien comes out of retirement to keep the legendary Green Destiny sword away from villainous warlord Hades Dai.</Description><Id>80039717</Id><Name>Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon: Sword of Destiny</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A simple man's peaceful life is complicated when an incident brings him in contact with a gangster and launches his journey into the underworld.</Description><Id>80201612</Id><Name>Daagdi Chaawl</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a realm where magic and technology intersect, a shifty, cigar-smoking wizard finds himself in the middle of a war with the powers of hell.</Description><Id>80142140</Id><Name>Daemonium</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a volcanologist comes to investigate the recent rumblings of a dormant volcano, a massive eruption has everyone in town fighting for their lives.</Description><Id>1151375</Id><Name>Dante's Peak</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To bring down a global human trafficking ring, an Interpol agent recruits the help of a brutal criminal with inside knowledge of the yakuza.</Description><Id>80232330</Id><Name>Darc</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An ex-racecar driver is sent to a barbaric prison where, to get pardoned, he must defeat the inmate known as Frankenstein in a lethal "Death Race."</Description><Id>80218973</Id><Name>Death Race: Beyond Anarchy</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this action-packed drama based on an extraordinary true story, four brothers protect more than 1,000 Jewish refugees during World War II.</Description><Id>70101696</Id><Name>Defiance</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Three flatmates get involved in the shady business belonging to one roomie's fiancé, and discover that a global crime syndicate is gunning for them.</Description><Id>70152959</Id><Name>Delhi Belly</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A man begins to regret his choices when his brother decides to join him as a member of the same terrorist organization.</Description><Id>81035835</Id><Name>Detention Letter</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Tipped off about buried money in Goa, four ne’er-do-well friends go on the hunt, chased by a police officer who wants the treasure for himself.</Description><Id>81213888</Id><Name>Dhamaal</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Framed by an empress who plans to steal a dragon-taming mace, imperial magistrate Dee Renjie soon uncovers a greater plot that threatens the kingdom.</Description><Id>81010962</Id><Name>Di Renjie zhi Sidatianwang</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Pierce Brosnan's final outing as 007 finds James Bond facing off against a North Korean terrorist who's in league with a British diamond merchant.</Description><Id>60024927</Id><Name>Die Another Day</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young couple falls in love, but conflicting loyalties drive them apart. Years later, fate intervenes and hands them a second chance.</Description><Id>80091866</Id><Name>Dilwale</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Shaolin monk San Te returns to protect a fellow hero with a talent for finding trouble in this action-packed sequel to "The 36th Chamber of Shaolin."</Description><Id>80039484</Id><Name>Disciples Of The 36th Chamber</Name><ReleaseYear>1985</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After years of segregation and forced labor, a race of stranded aliens enlists in a resistance movement spearheaded by a rogue government agent.</Description><Id>70113005</Id><Name>District 9</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A man who's a lookalike for a slain mob kingpin is asked by the police to impersonate the gangster and infiltrate his underworld organization.</Description><Id>20255837</Id><Name>Don</Name><ReleaseYear>1978</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A ruthless crime boss and drug lord is nabbed and held captive by the authorities, who send his naïve look-alike to infiltrate the man's gang.</Description><Id>70059026</Id><Name>Don</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>With Asia under his complete control, criminal mastermind Don turns to Europe, battling the mob bosses of each nation along the way.</Description><Id>70224999</Id><Name>Don 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a swarm of soul-stealing demons invades a Martian moon, a group of elite space Marines must obliterate the beasts to save Earth.</Description><Id>81164603</Id><Name>Doom: Annihilation</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When the tenant in their flat dies under suspicious circumstances, two bickering cousins are forced to navigate both sides of the law.</Description><Id>80997858</Id><Name>Doubles Cause Troubles</Name><ReleaseYear>1989</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Dragon and his fellow students at Dragon Tiger Gate martial arts school team up to battle the ferocious villain Shibumi.</Description><Id>70082255</Id><Name>Dragon Tiger Gate</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In ancient times when majestic fire-breathers soared through the skies, a knight comes face to face and heart to heart with the last dragon on Earth.</Description><Id>60029363</Id><Name>Dragonheart</Name><ReleaseYear>1996</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When an aspiring knight crosses paths with a dragon, the two form an unlikely alliance in a high-stakes battle against a malicious sorcerer.</Description><Id>80032636</Id><Name>Dragonheart 3: The Sorcerer</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This sequel introduces Draco the dragon's offspring, Drake, who dreams of becoming a knight and teams up with a stable boy to master his skills.</Description><Id>60002003</Id><Name>Dragonheart: A New Beginning</Name><ReleaseYear>2000</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When the king of Brittania dies, the dragon who shares his heart must find a new ruler, but the monarch's grandchildren go to war over the throne.</Description><Id>80176756</Id><Name>Dragonheart: Battle for the Heartfire</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A Hollywood stuntman and getaway driver is lured from his isolated life by a lovely neighbor – until her violent husband is released from prison.</Description><Id>70189289</Id><Name>Drive</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A notorious thief allies with a street racer for a grand heist involving an elaborate game of deceit with authorities, who have their own dirty secrets.</Description><Id>81189912</Id><Name>Drive</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When one of his colleagues becomes corrupted by power and goes over to the dark side, a young police officer tries to bring the offender to justice.</Description><Id>60036617</Id><Name>Dum</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A security expert and ex-CIA agent living in Belgium must go on the run with his estranged teen daughter when they're both marked for assassination.</Description><Id>70252885</Id><Name>El último testigo</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Journalist Naresh is hired to probe illegal activities on an island. When he's captured, a fellow prisoner gives him a ring with magic powers.</Description><Id>80158482</Id><Name>Elaan</Name><ReleaseYear>1971</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Officers Taylor and Zavala patrol the streets of South Central Los Angeles, an area of the city ruled by gangs and riddled with drug violence.</Description><Id>70235384</Id><Name>End of Watch</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Recruited by a British agent, Shaolin master Lee infiltrates a remote island and a brutal martial arts tournament to spy on a sinister crime lord.</Description><Id>60036838</Id><Name>Enter the Dragon</Name><ReleaseYear>1973</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An avid gamer is magically transported to ancient China, where he must become a warrior in order to save the princess from an evil warlord.</Description><Id>80138681</Id><Name>Enter the Warriors Gate</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a dystopian future, a totalitarian regime maintains peace by subduing the populace with a drug, and displays of emotion are punishable by death.</Description><Id>60024935</Id><Name>Equilibrium</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Fifteen years after the Second Impact, apathetic teen Shinji joins his father's group NERV to fight the Angels. But the truth may destroy them all.</Description><Id>81033473</Id><Name>EVANGELION: DEATH (TRUE)²</Name><ReleaseYear>1998</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When terrorists hijack a 747 and turn it into a nerve gas bomb aimed at Washington, D.C., commandos use an experimental plane to try to stop them.</Description><Id>485218</Id><Name>Executive Decision</Name><ReleaseYear>1996</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Maverick cop Orin Boyd joins forces with an unlikely ally in gangster Latrell Walker to take down a group of dirty Detroit cops.</Description><Id>60020892</Id><Name>Exit Wounds</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In the wake of a global catastrophe, the human survivors are "uploaded" into a cyber network, but someone or something is infiltrating the system.</Description><Id>80038207</Id><Name>Expelled from Paradise</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Mistakenly accused of kidnapping, a veteran soldier leaves a trail of broken bad guys in his wake as he tries to rescue a teen sex trafficking victim.</Description><Id>81167494</Id><Name>Expo</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Plagued by dreams of an alien invasion, a family man faces his worst nightmare when an extraterrestrial force begins exterminating Earth's inhabitants.</Description><Id>80236421</Id><Name>Extinction</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young man enlists the help of his friends to avenge his uncle's death by taking on a powerful, unscrupulous politician.</Description><Id>80202087</Id><Name>Fakta Ladh Mhana</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a man is arrested on arrival in America because authorities mistake him for a wanted gangster, a new friend tries to help him prove his innocence.</Description><Id>81024716</Id><Name>Faraar</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A stock broker brings his young son back to the town where he grew up for a hunting trip, but things take a dangerous turn when they witness a crime.</Description><Id>80187228</Id><Name>First Kill</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When five ninjas whose fighting styles are based on natural elements unleash their fury on a rival school, a lone survivor vows deadly revenge.</Description><Id>70124316</Id><Name>Five Elements Ninjas</Name><ReleaseYear>1982</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The emperor's reign of terror expands. Heroic outlaw Ma Teng joins a squad of female rebels, whose leader is torn between family loyalties.</Description><Id>80997870</Id><Name>Flying Guillotine 2</Name><ReleaseYear>1978</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A pulp-fiction sci-fi classic, Forbidden Planet stars Leslie Nielsen as a heroic starship captain who finds the paradise planet Altair-IV.</Description><Id>516788</Id><Name>Forbidden Planet</Name><ReleaseYear>1956</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An ex-cop investigates the death of his best friend and two other spies, killings that lead to a mole operating from India's embassy in Budapest.</Description><Id>80159955</Id><Name>Force 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A sketchy arms transaction in a deserted warehouse turns into a free-for-all when the two sides engage in a take-no-prisoners shootout.</Description><Id>80091310</Id><Name>Free Fire</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A low-level intelligence agent gets pulled into action and espionage above his pay grade when he's ordered to assist a trigger-happy senior agent.</Description><Id>70117322</Id><Name>From Paris with Love</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Four young male friends tackle the challenges and unexpected catastrophes of growing up clueless in this music-packed Bollywood teen drama.</Description><Id>70278990</Id><Name>Fukrey</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While alchemist Edward Elric searches for a way to restore his brother Al's body, the military government and mysterious monsters are watching closely.</Description><Id>80223731</Id><Name>FullMetal Alchemist</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When traffickers kidnap her daughter from their village, vengeful Hai Phuong returns to Saigon – and her outlaw roots – to take down the abductors.</Description><Id>81075519</Id><Name>Furie</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Carpet dealer and UFO photo forger Arif is abducted by aliens. On the planet Gora, he helps friends escape from a meteorite strike and find freedom.</Description><Id>80038440</Id><Name>G.O.R.A</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a vengeful college professor targets corruption in the government, he adopts the name "Gabbar" and becomes a hero to a weary public.</Description><Id>80057278</Id><Name>Gabbar Is Back</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Three buddies with big dreams go from underachieving slackers to badass warriors when their posh hotel is taken over by terrorists.</Description><Id>80169617</Id><Name>Game Over, Man!</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Teams of recently deceased people who've been revived and given high-tech weapons must cooperate to defeat an army of monsters in Tokyo and Osaka.</Description><Id>80149259</Id><Name>GANTZ:O</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a zealous gang leader plans to take out a friend-turned-rival for control of his turf, internal tensions complicate the battle to be the boss.</Description><Id>81072917</Id><Name>Gatao 2: Rise of the King</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When the identities of secret agents are compromised, hapless Maxwell Smart teams with far more capable Agent 99 to thwart an evil terrorist group.</Description><Id>70077557</Id><Name>Get Smart</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Framed for his older brother's murder, a boxer seeks violent revenge against the true killer who's torn his family apart.</Description><Id>20077944</Id><Name>Ghayal</Name><ReleaseYear>1990</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>World War IV is over, but a bomb has gone off in Newport City, killing a major arms dealer who may have ties with the mysterious 501 Organization.</Description><Id>80002073</Id><Name>Ghost Pain</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Stunt cyclist Johnny Blaze makes a bargain with the sinister Mephisto to save a loved one. Years later, Johnny gets the chance to reclaim his soul.</Description><Id>70044594</Id><Name>Ghost Rider</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As Motoko and Batou attempt to thwart a mysterious terrorist group, Togusa tracks the killer of a man with a prosthetic leg made by Mermaid's Leg.</Description><Id>80021983</Id><Name>Ghost Tears</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Freed of her responsibilities for the 501 Organization, Motoko must now learn how to take orders from Aramaki.</Description><Id>80002074</Id><Name>Ghost Whispers</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Giving up his life of crime for love, a gangster struggles with a moral dilemma when tragic events and enduring enemies take him back to the underworld.</Description><Id>20705133</Id><Name>Ghulam-E-Musthafa</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The girls of Oarai High must face off against a formidable university team in a fierce tank battle to once again avoid closure of their school.</Description><Id>80159876</Id><Name>Girls und Panzer der Film</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A maverick leader and a clever young general take on Japanese pirates amid bureaucratic intrigue in Ming Dynasty China.</Description><Id>80145625</Id><Name>God of War</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A team of experts – including a biologist and two scientists – must stop an oversized lizard from destroying all of Manhattan.</Description><Id>11819467</Id><Name>Godzilla</Name><ReleaseYear>1998</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>On Earth, Haruo and his companions make contact with the indigenous Houtua tribe. To defeat Godzilla, they set out for the old Mechagodzilla facility.</Description><Id>80180376</Id><Name>GODZILLA City on the Edge of Battle</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>With the earth alliance weakened, Haruo weighs siding with the Exif, whose death cult is summoning a monster that can destroy the world.</Description><Id>80198623</Id><Name>GODZILLA The Planet Eater</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Pierce Brosnan takes his first turn as debonair secret agent James Bond, who investigates the destruction of a Russian satellite weapons base.</Description><Id>22040803</Id><Name>GoldenEye</Name><ReleaseYear>1995</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Hapless brothers Gollu and Pappu stumble into a terrorist plot and end up being ordered to detonate a bomb, a task they are destined to bungle.</Description><Id>80165851</Id><Name>Gollu Aur Pappu</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A struggling couple can't believe their luck when they find a stash of money in the apartment of a neighbor who was recently murdered.</Description><Id>70304990</Id><Name>Good People</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An embittered cop is tasked with baby-sitting a spoiled actor, but the two must learn to fight together when they run afoul of a group of mercenaries.</Description><Id>80097221</Id><Name>Gridlocked</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A pampered but kind-hearted average joe ditches his romancing and peacekeeping ways when he’s framed for a murder he didn’t commit.</Description><Id>81217737</Id><Name>Guna 369</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this sequel, a group of expert drivers skilled in drifting and high-speed racing is recruited to perform obscure tasks for a shadowy gang.</Description><Id>81074140</Id><Name>Hajwala 2: Mysterious Mission</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A competitive streetcar racer's obsession with winning drive him to develop a vehicle with an innovative engine that's never been used before.</Description><Id>80202605</Id><Name>Hajwala: The Missing Engine</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This anthology features seven independent anime shorts from renowned directors, delving into the futuristic universe of the video game franchise Halo.</Description><Id>70129415</Id><Name>HALO Legends</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Witness the origins of Master Chief and the Spartan program as a group of children transform into enhanced soldiers and fight a powerful alien threat.</Description><Id>80079265</Id><Name>Halo: The Fall of Reach</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Vietnam War's horrors come brutally to life through the eyes of American soldiers trying to take a heavily fortified hill under Vietcong control.</Description><Id>569355</Id><Name>Hamburger Hill</Name><ReleaseYear>1987</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A revenge-seeking diamond thief gathers a ragtag crew to infiltrate a Dubai hotel hosting a dance contest. But first they have to learn how to dance.</Description><Id>80017528</Id><Name>Happy New Year</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A millionaire opens the door to comic complications when he punishes his spoiled sons for trying to make money through shady, get-rich-quick schemes.</Description><Id>70021253</Id><Name>Haseena Maan Jaayegi</Name><ReleaseYear>1999</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a young man wakes from a coma, memories of brutal violence begin to surface, putting his life – and that of his doctor – in jeopardy.</Description><Id>80109145</Id><Name>Headshot</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When master criminal Helios steals a mobile WMD, rival agents from Hong Kong, South Korea and China must join forces to recover the device.</Description><Id>80106306</Id><Name>Helios</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When best friends break a blood oath, one of them is cast away to hell, and the other two must save him from the misfits of the underworld.</Description><Id>80058026</Id><Name>Hell and Back</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This fast-paced action flick tells the dark story of Hellboy, a charismatic demon who's put on Earth by the Nazis to terrorize the rest of the world.</Description><Id>60034549</Id><Name>Hellboy</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The bond between two crooks and best friends is threatened when one learns that the other's father had a hand in his own tragic past.</Description><Id>20765027</Id><Name>Hera Pheri</Name><ReleaseYear>1976</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A pugilist from Shantung struggles to rise to the top of the Shanghai triad ladder, where his stellar martial arts talents can shine.</Description><Id>80039485</Id><Name>Hero</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When its special ops agency is wiped out, Spain hastily assembles a new team to defuse a terrorist plot. But who are these scrappy would-be heroes?</Description><Id>80093105</Id><Name>Heroes Wanted</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While serving as the marshal of rowdy Abilene, Kansas, "Wild Bill" Hickok uses guns and gall to tidy up the lawless frontier town.</Description><Id>80191109</Id><Name>Hickok</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>City girl Veera is kidnapped on the eve of her wedding, but as her captors take her through the countryside, Veera finds herself feeling emancipated.</Description><Id>70303424</Id><Name>Highway</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young man returns to his native village on a mission of vengeance after his father commits suicide in the wake of false accusations.</Description><Id>70254349</Id><Name>Himmatwala</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Determined to get his fiancée to L.A. to take advantage of an amazing opportunity, Charlie breaks out of the witness protection program to drive her.</Description><Id>70243445</Id><Name>Hit &amp; Run</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In the grim Alaskan winter, a naturalist hunts for wolves blamed for killing a local boy, but he soon finds himself swept into a chilling mystery.</Description><Id>80157072</Id><Name>Hold the Dark</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a mysterious disaster turns the country into a war zone, a young lawyer heads west with his future father-in-law to find his pregnant fiancée.</Description><Id>80167481</Id><Name>How It Ends</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This action-packed animated double feature pits the Hulk against two of the Marvel Universe's most powerful characters: Wolverine and Thor.</Description><Id>70111265</Id><Name>Hulk Vs.</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>U.S. Border Patrol agent and deadly hunter Jim Rhodes takes violent revenge when a group of desperate thieves kidnaps his daughter after a robbery.</Description><Id>70150473</Id><Name>Hunt to Kill</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A hired gun has second thoughts when he's contracted to kill a teenage girl whose father's shady business dealings put her life in danger.</Description><Id>70295169</Id><Name>Hunter's Prayer</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After learning that an ex-military friend and his parents were killed, the highly trained John Gold comes to town seeking answers and revenge.</Description><Id>80989338</Id><Name>I Am Vengeance</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Hell-bent on avenging his wife's murder, Stanley Hill summons an old partner's help in exposing a cover-up by crooked cops and slimy politicians.</Description><Id>80058248</Id><Name>I Am Wrath</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Four hundred years after they were frozen in time, a Ming Dynasty guard and his three pursuers are defrosted to continue their ancient battle.</Description><Id>80003479</Id><Name>Iceman</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In 2029, the elite police squad Illang combats a terrorist group opposing reunification of the two Koreas. But another enemy may be lurking nearby.</Description><Id>80239666</Id><Name>Illang: The Wolf Brigade</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a brawl lands him in a Boys’ Home, a teen seems to be on a promising path until loyalty to his gangster buddy leads to even bigger trouble.</Description><Id>81036532</Id><Name>Imperfect</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A naive and sheltered young woman embarks on a whimsical adventure across Italy in the hopes of meeting director Federico Fellini.</Description><Id>80189216</Id><Name>In Search of Fellini</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this mind-bending sci-fi thriller, a man runs an espionage business built around entering the subconscious of his targets to mold their thoughts.</Description><Id>70131314</Id><Name>Inception</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When an imprisoned terrorist cell hijacks a high-security prison in outer space, a CIA agent becomes the one chance of stopping them.</Description><Id>80202352</Id><Name>Incoming</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Indiana Jones is drawn into a Russian plot to unearth the Crystal Skulls of Akator, Amazonian artifacts with supernatural powers.</Description><Id>70084799</Id><Name>Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Accompanied by his father, Indiana Jones sets off on his third adventure to explore the cradle of civilization on a perilous hunt for the Holy Grail.</Description><Id>60010487</Id><Name>Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade</Name><ReleaseYear>1989</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When Indiana Jones is hired by the government to locate the legendary Ark of the Covenant, he finds himself up against the entire Nazi regime.</Description><Id>60011649</Id><Name>Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark</Name><ReleaseYear>1981</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Indiana Jones, his young sidekick and a spoiled songbird get more than they bargained for when they go to India in search of a missing magical stone.</Description><Id>60010488</Id><Name>Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom</Name><ReleaseYear>1984</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A Jewish cinema owner in occupied Paris is forced to host a Nazi premiere, where a group of American soldiers called the Basterds plans a face-off.</Description><Id>70108777</Id><Name>Inglourious Basterds</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>By day, an 18-year-old delivers tofu for his father, a retired race car driver; but by night, it's the teen's turn to take the wheel.</Description><Id>70043379</Id><Name>Initial D</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Unbeknownst to his 12-year-old daughter, a bookbinder has a secret ability to bring characters to life by reading their stories out loud.</Description><Id>70101345</Id><Name>Inkheart</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A grieving policeman and a rickshaw driver are brought together by a dark, tragic secret that will change their lives forever.</Description><Id>70025303</Id><Name>Insan</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A hotshot NYPD negotiator butts heads with the FBI and meets his match in a meticulous criminal mastermind as she attempts to rob the Federal Reserve.</Description><Id>81053953</Id><Name>Inside Man: Most Wanted</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Great Dog Demon beaqueathed one of the Three Swords of the Fang to each of his two sons. Now the evil power of the third sword has been awakened.</Description><Id>70036200</Id><Name>Inuyasha the Movie - La spada del dominatore del mondo</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Ai, a young half-demon who has escaped from Horai Island to try to help his people, returns with potential saviors InuYasha, Sesshomaru and Kikyo.</Description><Id>70052492</Id><Name>Inuyasha the Movie - L'isola del fuoco scarlatto</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A powerful demon has been sealed away for 200 years. But when the demon's son is awakened, the fate of the world is in jeopardy.</Description><Id>70012316</Id><Name>InuYasha the Movie: Affections Touching Across Time</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>With their biggest foe seemingly defeated, InuYasha and his friends return to everyday life. But the peace is soon shattered by an emerging new enemy.</Description><Id>70018513</Id><Name>InuYasha: The Movie 2: The Castle Beyond the Looking Glass</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An occupying Japanese general challenges Chinese men to duels to prove the superiority of the Japanese, but Ip Man refuses to fight – at first.</Description><Id>70118799</Id><Name>Ip Man</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>New in Hong Kong, martial arts instructor Ip Man perseveres and retaliates against his rivals' opposition to the Wing Chun fighting style he teaches.</Description><Id>70137753</Id><Name>Ip Man 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Martial arts master Ip springs into action when his son's school is threatened by a shady American, then defends his status as wing chun champion.</Description><Id>80076698</Id><Name>Ip Man 3</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Decades after a nuclear war, survivors on the moon revisit Earth to locate a potential power source – and find shape-shifting reptiles instead.</Description><Id>81132624</Id><Name>Iron Sky: The Coming Race</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a mysterious woman hires Shankar to spy on a family, he must determine how his own father's abandonment figures into the situation.</Description><Id>80157086</Id><Name>Jaal</Name><ReleaseYear>1986</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An eccentric, self-proclaimed detective goes on an action-packed hunt for his missing father, with an awkward but adventurous journalist by his side.</Description><Id>80104130</Id><Name>Jagga Jasoos</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Four cops escorting a mobster to a high-security prison fight for survival when a gang boss orchestrates a riot from outside to silence their charge.</Description><Id>80990658</Id><Name>Jailbreak</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a U.S. senator’s son is held captive by Hezbollah militiamen, a group of highly trained soldiers ventures into enemy territory to bring him home.</Description><Id>81164636</Id><Name>Jarhead: Law of Return</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Falling in with a band of outlaws during a holy pilgrimage, a country boy tries to change their violent ways ahead of a showdown with the authorities.</Description><Id>60001407</Id><Name>Jis Desh Men Ganga Behti Hai</Name><ReleaseYear>1960</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In 16th-century India, what begins as a strategic alliance between a Mughal emperor and a Hindu princess becomes a genuine opportunity for true love.</Description><Id>70090035</Id><Name>Jodhaa Akbar</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>One minute, Civil War veteran John Carter is evading Apaches; the next, he's waking up on Mars, a once-fruitful planet that's devolved into chaos.</Description><Id>70143369</Id><Name>John Carter</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The wounds of a traumatic childhood and a corrupt, unjust system push a young man into becoming a cold-blooded, ruthless gangster.</Description><Id>80228146</Id><Name>Jora 10 Numbaria</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Separated at birth, twins Raja and Prem couldn't be more different. But when fate puts them both in London, they start being mistaken for each other.</Description><Id>80236906</Id><Name>Judwaa 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young impoverished woman learns she's been predestined to change the fate of the universe after a genetically engineered hunter tracks her down.</Description><Id>70301367</Id><Name>Jupiter Ascending</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Slick lawyer Sung fears he's been cursed with bad karma and considers giving up his practice – until he's approached by a widow accused of murder.</Description><Id>70033611</Id><Name>Justice, My Foot!</Name><ReleaseYear>1992</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>On board Russia's first nuclear ballistic submarine, Capt. Vostrikov must race against time to prevent a Chernobyl-like explosion.</Description><Id>60023606</Id><Name>K-19: The Widowmaker</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Jailed for robbing his brother’s unscrupulous employer, a simpleton has a transformation while in prison, emerging with a violent mission for revenge.</Description><Id>20712279</Id><Name>Kaalia</Name><ReleaseYear>1981</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this Hindi version of the Tamil blockbuster, a Tamil gang leader in Kuala Lumpur seeks justice for crimes committed against him and his family.</Description><Id>80227673</Id><Name>Kabali (Hindi Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A prison guard goes undercover as a dancer to try and recapture an escaped criminal and restore her police inspector boyfriend's reputation.</Description><Id>17969262</Id><Name>Khalnayak</Name><ReleaseYear>1993</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As a crazed killer blazes a trail of blood through an anxious city, a hardened cop aims to take him down by any means in this remake of “Dirty Harry.”</Description><Id>80158480</Id><Name>Khoon Khoon</Name><ReleaseYear>1973</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Sloan's vow to never return to Thailand is cut short when he's kidnapped and taken to a Thai prison, where he's forced to fight a 400-pound brute.</Description><Id>80164088</Id><Name>Kickboxer: Retaliation</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a skilled fighter falls in the ring, his younger brother emerges from the shadows to train and get revenge against a brutal champion.</Description><Id>80103392</Id><Name>Kickboxer: Vengeance</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When beer magnate Alfred "Freddy" Heineken is kidnapped in 1983, his abductors make the largest ransom demand in history.</Description><Id>70299204</Id><Name>Kidnapping Mr. Heineken</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An assassin is shot by her ruthless employer, Bill, and other members of their assassination circle. But she lives – and plots her vengeance.</Description><Id>60031236</Id><Name>Kill Bill: Vol. 1</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Bride has three left on her rampage list: Budd, Elle Driver and Bill himself. But when she arrives at Bill's house, she's in for a surprise.</Description><Id>60032563</Id><Name>Kill Bill: Vol. 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>On a remote island, elite soldiers discover their training exercise is actually an experimental death trap teeming with efficiently lethal robots.</Description><Id>80100261</Id><Name>Kill Command</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Posing as a telecom salesman at a business conference, a CIA agent fights to protect a fledgling Eastern European democracy from a military coup.</Description><Id>80107808</Id><Name>Kill Ratio</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This true crime tale charts the rise and fall of mobster Danny Greene, who faced down the Mafia to gain control of organized crime in 1970s Cleveland.</Description><Id>70128697</Id><Name>Kill the Irishman</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two young men with disabilities befriend a hitman in a wheelchair and become his helpers, only to wind up in the crosshairs of a Serbian mobster.</Description><Id>80147758</Id><Name>Kills on Wheels</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A wealthy, despicable businessman comes to the realization that he may lose half his fortune to the obnoxious wife he's trying to divorce. So, he decides to arrange his own kidnapping in order to wipe himself out and claim poverty.</Description><Id>70020947</Id><Name>King's Ransom</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A bitter family battle ensues between a father and his sons when a businessman makes a deal that entices farmers to sell off their properties.</Description><Id>70125882</Id><Name>Kisaan</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>With five loyal friends in tow, explorer Thor Heyerdahl sails a fragile balsa wood raft along an ancient path some 4,300 miles across the Pacific.</Description><Id>70260989</Id><Name>Kon-Tiki</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>True love is put to the test when another woman comes between a pair of star-crossed young lovers in this thriller.</Description><Id>70025612</Id><Name>Krishna Cottage</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Sing, a mobster in 1940s China, longs to be as cool as the formally clad Axe Gang, a band of killers who rule Hong Kong, but can only pretend.</Description><Id>70020728</Id><Name>Kung Fu Hustle</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two mismatched archaeologists battle a team of vicious mercenaries in a race to discover an ancient Tibetan treasure of unimaginable worth.</Description><Id>80170301</Id><Name>Kung Fu Yoga</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a gun-toting rebel tries to rescue her kidnapped sister, she finds herself up against a widely feared desperado and a cursed guardian of treasure.</Description><Id>81091378</Id><Name>La Leyenda del Diamante</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An American travels to Hong Kong in hopes of winning a lucrative – but potentially deadly – all-female underground fighting tournament.</Description><Id>80167488</Id><Name>Lady Bloodfight</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After dropping out of the army, a spoiled teenager reenlists and proves his mettle by becoming an officer just as war breaks out.</Description><Id>70001237</Id><Name>Lakshya</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An ex-CIA contractor turned thief is forced to head a CIA gambit to infiltrate a black ops Mexican prison and steal $50 million in drug cartel money.</Description><Id>80192014</Id><Name>Larceny</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A nobleman who values his people's well-being over his emperor's edicts is killed. His knights vow revenge.</Description><Id>80014727</Id><Name>Last Knights</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After millions of people on Earth suddenly disappear, a pilot flying a plane stuck at 30,000 feet must find a way to ensure the passengers' survival.</Description><Id>80013773</Id><Name>Left Behind</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A petty thief teams up with two bickering accomplices to safeguard a powerful relic and save humankind from a tribe of vengeful, winged humanoids.</Description><Id>80201200</Id><Name>Legend of the Naga Pearls</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Three assassins – magician Lei Ying, hit man Tieh Hon and kung fu master Ti Tan – are sent to Yunnan by their clan leader to bring to justice another clan member who betrayed the tribe.</Description><Id>70059191</Id><Name>Legendary Weapons of China</Name><ReleaseYear>1982</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A motley crew of apocalypse survivors living at an abandoned truck stop never suspects that the pregnant woman among them is carrying the Messiah.</Description><Id>70117305</Id><Name>Legion</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Cole finds himself trapped in Yang's temple after accidentally releasing a host of villainous spirits that the Ninja must defeat.</Description><Id>81048910</Id><Name>LEGO Ninjago: Masters of Spinjitzu: Day of the Departed</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A vengeful son, a cop on a mission, a wannabe actress and a jilted lover find their lives intermingling in unexpected ways over 24 hours in Mumbai.</Description><Id>81024730</Id><Name>Life Ki Toh Lag Gayi</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Johnnie To's character-centered drama follows a Hong Kong firefighting crew as they take on harrowing rescue missions and navigate personal dilemmas.</Description><Id>11546798</Id><Name>Lifeline</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>With his writing career dragging, Eddie Morra finds his life turning around after he takes a drug that provides astonishing mental focus.</Description><Id>70142827</Id><Name>Limitless</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A Hong Kong intelligence officer tasked with finding undercover agents whose identities have been erased finds herself in the paths of rival triads.</Description><Id>80135353</Id><Name>Line Walker</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Kidnapped as a child and raised in the circus, a young lion tamer’s tough side emerges when he gets entangled in an underworld murder mystery.</Description><Id>81035855</Id><Name>Lion's Heart</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Seeking to improve his combat skills, a young man falls in love with a woman with mystical powers, but his past stands in the way of their union.</Description><Id>80997864</Id><Name>Little Dragon Maiden</Name><ReleaseYear>1983</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Hoping to make a bundle in a high-stakes poker game, four shiftless lads from London's East End instead find themselves swimming in debt.</Description><Id>16944044</Id><Name>Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels</Name><ReleaseYear>1998</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After getting in a fight at her school in Southeast Asia, an American teen is sent to a correctional facility, where she faces hard labor and abuse.</Description><Id>80190215</Id><Name>Locked Up</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In the 23rd century, inhabitants of a domed city exist in a world filled with life's pleasures – but no one is allowed to live past the age of 30.</Description><Id>709163</Id><Name>Logan's Run</Name><ReleaseYear>1976</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An officer killed on the job returns to Earth as a ghost to solve his own murder and seek justice with the help of a rookie cop and some funky magic.</Description><Id>70014531</Id><Name>Look Out, Officer</Name><ReleaseYear>1990</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To prove himself to a love interest, a delivery boy learns dubious kung fu from an aging charlatan so he can challenge his archrival to a fight.</Description><Id>70026792</Id><Name>Love on Delivery</Name><ReleaseYear>1994</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Lupin, his sidekick, Jigen, and the samurai warrior Goemon set out to take over an evil counterfeit operation at Count Cagliostro's fortress.</Description><Id>70050576</Id><Name>Lupin the 3rd: The Castle of Cagliostro: Special Edition</Name><ReleaseYear>1979</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two young brothers encounter a singing bird who treats them to a musical reinterpretation of one of India’s most epic ancient tales.</Description><Id>81002214</Id><Name>Mahabharat</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Major Ram Prasad Sharma yearns to see project Mission Milaap come to fruition and usher in an era of peace between two warring countries. But the evil Raghavan will do anything to stop the peace process.</Description><Id>70000196</Id><Name>Main Hoon Na</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this kung fu tale set in Beijing, a young man armed with incomparable martial arts skills gets embroiled in the world of underground fight clubs.</Description><Id>70278930</Id><Name>Man of Tai Chi</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A Chinese pharmaceutical lawyer framed for a vile crime teams up with a sharp-witted Japanese detective to stop a dangerous corporate plot.</Description><Id>80209866</Id><Name>Manhunt</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An ex-assassin tries to leave her dark past behind until a power-hungry gang targets her and her family, forcing her to summon her killer instincts.</Description><Id>80236341</Id><Name>Maria</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In ancient China, Zhi Ming trains at the legendary Northern Shaolin temple to avenge the death of his father at the hands of a nefarious magistrate.</Description><Id>80039662</Id><Name>Martial Arts of Shaolin</Name><ReleaseYear>1986</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When scientists join Hulk's gamma energy with Tony Stark's Arc Reactor, the resulting force creates a foe that only the two Marvel heroes can combat.</Description><Id>70295085</Id><Name>Marvel's Iron Man &amp; Hulk: Heroes United</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Needing hard evidence to convict a company chairman of fraud, an investigator bargains with the company's tech expert to turn over his boss's ledger.</Description><Id>80163352</Id><Name>Master</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this spin-off, a martial arts expert once defeated by Ip Man is forced to abandon his reclusive lifestyle to combat a rising Chinese triad.</Description><Id>81071891</Id><Name>Master Z: The Ip Man Legacy</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An unconventional police officer faces off against a gang of thugs as he tries to bring order to the far-flung village he’s been stationed in.</Description><Id>81113926</Id><Name>Mauli</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A streetwise cop teams with a veteran government agent to work for a super-secret, extremely dapper team that monitors extraterrestrials on Earth.</Description><Id>60001650</Id><Name>Men in Black</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Will Smith and Tommy Lee Jones reprise their roles as two highly secretive and unofficial government agents dealing with all things evil and alien.</Description><Id>60023597</Id><Name>Men in Black II</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this fast-paced Indonesian thriller, a young martial arts master travels to Jakarta, where he saves an orphan from a human-trafficking ring.</Description><Id>70118368</Id><Name>Merantau</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A detective arrests a doctor for crimes targeting medical professionals but later finds the real culprit in a tale of revenge, corruption and magic.</Description><Id>81016196</Id><Name>Mersal</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Mysterious goons chase teenage slacker Angelino through chaotic Dark Meat City as he uncovers secret powers that could be the key to saving the world.</Description><Id>81037697</Id><Name>MFKZ</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a terrorist escapes custody, MI-5 director Harry Pearce becomes the scapegoat. But the wily veteran still has some spycraft tricks up his sleeve.</Description><Id>80081505</Id><Name>MI-5</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A television journalist makes a risky career move by accepting a job offer from a controversial Istanbul television station.</Description><Id>70109375</Id><Name>Mission Istaanbul: Darr Ke Aagey Jeet Hai</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As Hitler's Nazis threaten to take command of Britain's skies, a squadron of Polish pilots arrives to aid the Royal Air Force against a mutual enemy.</Description><Id>80198632</Id><Name>Mission of Honor</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>During the War of 1812, two Native Americans and their British ally are pursued into enemy territory by American soldiers thirsting for revenge.</Description><Id>80220676</Id><Name>Mohawk</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A courageous villager moves to the ancient city of Mohenjo Daro, where he falls for the daughter of a priest and does battle with a tyrant.</Description><Id>80104257</Id><Name>Mohenjo Daro</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>TV news reporter James Russell helps put small-time criminal Franklin Hatchett in jail, but turns to protecting Hatchett when he escapes from prison.</Description><Id>1179583</Id><Name>Money Talks</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An American platoon stationed in the Middle East is thrust into battle with a breed of tentacled aliens whose rapid spread threatens human survival.</Description><Id>70253597</Id><Name>Monsters: Dark Continent</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Monty Python comedy clan skewers King Arthur and his Knights of the Round Table as they quest far and wide for the Holy Grail.</Description><Id>771476</Id><Name>Monty Python and the Holy Grail</Name><ReleaseYear>1975</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A brain-addled war vet, a failing band manager and a Stanley Kubrick impersonator help the CIA construct an epic scam by faking the 1969 moon landing.</Description><Id>80046728</Id><Name>Moonwalkers</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Featuring breathtaking imagery and thought-provoking narration, this film takes viewers to the summits of some of the world’s most amazing mountains.</Description><Id>80221498</Id><Name>Mountain</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An orphaned boy raised by animals in the jungle seizes his destiny while confronting a dangerous enemy – and his own human origins.</Description><Id>80993105</Id><Name>Mowgli: Legend of the Jungle</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A martial arts specialist accidentally becomes a superhero when he steps in – in costume – to help the cops catch a criminal.</Description><Id>70229047</Id><Name>Mugamoodi</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Jailed as a teenager, Shankar has been unable to stay on the right side of the law ever since, despite his wife's pleas and his mother's rejection.</Description><Id>80156939</Id><Name>Mujrim</Name><ReleaseYear>1989</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When jingle composer Nanda's car breaks down on his way to Chennai, he hitchhikes there with Arjun, who tries to rope Nanda into a shady deal.</Description><Id>70229555</Id><Name>Muran</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Marlon Brando gives a nuanced performance as the aristocratic Lt. Fletcher Christian, an officer aboard the HMS Bounty who leads a mutiny against the ship's tyrannical Capt. Bligh.</Description><Id>60011729</Id><Name>Mutiny on the Bounty</Name><ReleaseYear>1962</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A brainy private school student is transferred to a far less elite institution, where he must fend off classmates who settle scores with fistfights.</Description><Id>60027334</Id><Name>My Schoolmate, the Barbarian</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A bullied student forms a bond with the leader of a youth gang and discovers the power and meaning of true friendship.</Description><Id>80999987</Id><Name>My True Friend</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A fiery young woman accepts help from a spy agency to avenge her lover's murder. In return, she must prove herself as one of their top recruits.</Description><Id>80177776</Id><Name>Naam Shabana</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After his sleeping disorder hinders him from protecting his girlfriend, a man sets out to take revenge on the thugs who attacked her.</Description><Id>80190103</Id><Name>Naan Sigappu Manithan</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While loyally defending his boss from mobsters trying to kill him, a naive, hotel bellboy discovers the family he never knew he had.</Description><Id>81213897</Id><Name>Namak Halaal</Name><ReleaseYear>1982</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Mistakenly accused of an attack on the Fourth Raikage, ninja Naruto is imprisoned in the impenetrable Hozuki Castle and his powers are sealed.</Description><Id>80152537</Id><Name>Naruto Shippuden : Blood Prison</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When strange ninjas ambush the village of Konohagakure, it's up to adolescent ninja Naruto and his long-missing pal, Sasuke, to save the planet.</Description><Id>70105699</Id><Name>Naruto Shippûden the Movie: Bonds</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When four out of five ninja villages are destroyed, the leader of the one spared tries to find the true culprit and protect his land.</Description><Id>80045673</Id><Name>Naruto Shippûden the Movie: The Will of Fire</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The adventures of adolescent ninja Naruto Uzumaki continue as he's tasked with protecting a priestess from a demon – but to do so, he must die.</Description><Id>70124999</Id><Name>Naruto Shippuden: The Movie</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When Naruto is sent to recover a missing nin, the rogue manages to send him 20 years into the past, where he unites with his father to battle evil.</Description><Id>70275937</Id><Name>Naruto Shippuden: The Movie: The Lost Tower</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While on a mission to return a missing pet, Naruto and two fellow ninjas are ambushed by brutal knights led by the enigmatic Temujin.</Description><Id>70101321</Id><Name>Naruto the Movie 2: Legend of the Stone of Gelel</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Exuberant ninja Naruto teams up with his pals Sakura and Kakashi to escort Prince Michiru and his son, Hikaru, to the Crescent Moon kingdom.</Description><Id>70108386</Id><Name>Naruto the Movie 3: Guardians of the Crescent Moon Kingdom</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Naruto, Sasuke and Sakura learn they'll be protecting an actress from being hurt while making her next film, but it turns out she's a princess.</Description><Id>70074559</Id><Name>Naruto the Movie: Ninja Clash in the Land of Snow</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this parody of the Lethal Weapon franchise, criminals murder a detective and steal her prized evidence: microfilm with a recipe for cocaine cookies. Luckily, loose-cannon cop Jack Colt and his by-the-book partner, Wes Luger, are on the case.</Description><Id>22497725</Id><Name>National Lampoon's Loaded Weapon 1</Name><ReleaseYear>1993</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Modern treasure hunters search for a chest of riches rumored to have been stashed away by George Washington, Thomas Jefferson and Benjamin Franklin.</Description><Id>70011206</Id><Name>National Treasure</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When her friend’s rapist evades punishment from the law, a determined young woman takes revenge into her own hands in this story based on real events.</Description><Id>81024711</Id><Name>Needhi Singh</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Las Vegas magician Cris can see a few minutes into the future and an FBI agent wants his help thwarting a nuclear attack.</Description><Id>70066433</Id><Name>Next</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>With numbers written on a doll as their only clue, three officers of the law track down a psychotic killer, unearthing dark secrets along the way.</Description><Id>80206732</Id><Name>Nibunan</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his best friend is murdered by the shadowy Ozunu clan, Raizo, an orphan raised to be an assassin, vows revenge.</Description><Id>70101697</Id><Name>Ninja Assassin</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two average teens go on a magical quest to save the life of their friend and her counterpart from another world. But love complicates their journey.</Description><Id>81093113</Id><Name>NiNoKuni</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In ancient Disboard, a young warrior befriends an ex machina and embarks on a harrowing mission to stop a global war and save humanity from extinction.</Description><Id>81068687</Id><Name>No Game No Life: Zero</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When aliens take over their small Australian town, a modest group of survivors must unite to fend off their otherworldly intruders.</Description><Id>80220085</Id><Name>Occupation</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Frank Sinatra leads an all-star cast as Danny Ocean, who decides to knock over a few casinos on the Las Vegas Strip with his buddies.</Description><Id>60021590</Id><Name>Ocean's Eleven</Name><ReleaseYear>1960</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This entry in the all-star caper franchise finds debonair con man Danny Ocean and his gang taking revenge on a double-crossing Las Vegas kingpin.</Description><Id>70058024</Id><Name>Ocean's Thirteen</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Danny Ocean reunites with his old flame and the rest of his merry band of thieves in a caper covering three huge heists in Rome, Paris and Amsterdam.</Description><Id>70011211</Id><Name>Ocean's Twelve</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Fallen Los Angeles police officer Terrence Downe finds new life as a secret weapon: a scientifically altered super-cop with unlimited lives.</Description><Id>80145255</Id><Name>Officer Downe</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Competitive gamer Jan finds his life thrown for a loop when his bitter rival hacks his identity just before a high-stakes tournament.</Description><Id>80162197</Id><Name>Offline - Das leben ist kein bonuslevel</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A penniless actor new to Mumbai and a beautiful woman he meets one fateful night try to stop a gangster from replacing India's president with a twin.</Description><Id>80156937</Id><Name>Oh Darling Yeh Hai India</Name><ReleaseYear>1995</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A gentle giant and the girl who raised her are caught in the crossfire between animal activism, corporate greed and scientific ethics.</Description><Id>80091936</Id><Name>Okja</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A disgraced Secret Service agent must come to the rescue when Korean terrorists descend on the White House and take the president hostage.</Description><Id>70259801</Id><Name>Olympus Has Fallen</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two rebellious, hot-headed teenage brothers get caught up in gang life, which has dangerous repercussions for their family and friends.</Description><Id>80997865</Id><Name>On the Wrong Track</Name><ReleaseYear>1983</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two former triads are tapped to run in an election for leader of the underworld, but both want normal lives. Each must outwit the other to lose.</Description><Id>80127645</Id><Name>Once a Gangster</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this epic spaghetti Western, a flinty gunslinger is hired by a railroad tycoon to kill anyone standing in the way of his trans-American iron horse.</Description><Id>60031884</Id><Name>Once Upon a Time in the West</Name><ReleaseYear>1968</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his partner is killed, a young cop is forced to care for the man's four children, and solicits the help of a woman who moves in with them.</Description><Id>80156935</Id><Name>One 2 Ka 4</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a crime-plagued area of Rio de Janeiro, a team of honest cops, including a determined rookie, fights corruption and mistrust on all sides.</Description><Id>80071048</Id><Name>Operações Especiais</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To pave the way for a major amphibious invasion, a team of South Korean spies goes behind enemy lines to steal a map of North Korean coastal defenses.</Description><Id>80116307</Id><Name>Operation Chromite</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a dangerous area of the Mekong River, a drug raid ending in 13 deaths arouses the suspicions of a narcotics officer who sets out to find the truth.</Description><Id>80142222</Id><Name>Operation Mekong</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A special task force takes on a risky operation to evacuate civilians amid civil war. Based on the 2015 mission to rescue Chinese citizens in Yemen.</Description><Id>80239961</Id><Name>Operation Red Sea</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Leader of the Ten Kwangtung Tigers, Tieh Chiao-san works with his kung fu students to protect his village from crime. But when an opium dealer starts to ruin the town, Tieh Chiao-san struggles to fight back, thanks to his growing opium addiction.</Description><Id>70111922</Id><Name>Opium and the Kung Fu Master</Name><ReleaseYear>1984</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A gang leader recruits a suicidal Superman impersonator, while a woman driving a hot car linked to the gang plots revenge against them and their hero.</Description><Id>80038443</Id><Name>Organize Isler</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In 14th-century Scotland, Robert the Bruce claims the crown and leads a fierce uprising to win back the country's independence from English rule.</Description><Id>80190859</Id><Name>Outlaw King</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a failed mission, an ex-Royal Marines Commando tries to overcome his demons while investigating the death of his ex-girlfriend's father.</Description><Id>81026667</Id><Name>Outlawed</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While investigating a bank robbery, a squad of overweight police officers undergoes rigorous training to shed pounds.</Description><Id>80999996</Id><Name>Oversize Cops</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Paan Singh Tomar goes from celebrated runner to star brigand and rebel when life after sports fails to unfold as planned.</Description><Id>70123126</Id><Name>Paan Singh Tomar</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When profit-seekers threaten to take over a bar in a tourist town, local martial artists put their skills to the test and fight back.</Description><Id>80999986</Id><Name>Pahuyut Fighting Beat</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This fictionalized account of three real-life notorious Harlem drug dealers is told in flashbacks as they plunge into the world of hustling.</Description><Id>60023638</Id><Name>Paid in Full</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Looking for a way out of his impoverished life, a lowly hotel waiter joins an underground fight club. Then he needs a way out of that.</Description><Id>80202078</Id><Name>Pandigai</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Mehdi gets out of prison, planning to settle old scores. But first, he must reconnect with his gang, now living in an idyllic beach resort in Thailand.</Description><Id>81079723</Id><Name>Paradise Beach</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Naval unit PASKAL is among the most elite special forces in Malaysia. But all bets are off when one of its own stages a hijacking. Based on true events.</Description><Id>81031178</Id><Name>Paskal</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>CIA desk jockey Jack Ryan plunges into the heart of international terrorism after spoiling an assassination attempt on a British royal family member.</Description><Id>846071</Id><Name>Patriot Games</Name><ReleaseYear>1992</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An overzealous security guard finds himself in over his head when he tries to thwart a criminal mastermind's plot to rob an entire shopping mall.</Description><Id>70109689</Id><Name>Paul Blart: Mall Cop</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An affable, newly appointed college warden proves to be no ordinary man when an old enemy resurfaces and exposes his complicated, violent past.</Description><Id>81091423</Id><Name>Petta</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An affable, newly appointed college warden proves to be no ordinary man when an old enemy resurfaces and exposes his complicated, violent past.</Description><Id>81091424</Id><Name>Petta (Telugu Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>India's primary intelligence agency sends an enigmatic operative on a top-secret mission to avenge the 11/26 terrorist attack on Mumbai.</Description><Id>70303495</Id><Name>Phantom</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A boy whose illness allows him to float outside his body uses his newfound skill to help a cop take on a madman who's terrorizing New York City.</Description><Id>80063290</Id><Name>Phantom Boy</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Learning of a fortune in gold being secretly shipped to Romania, master thieves Charlie and Riya assemble a crack team to steal it.</Description><Id>70229498</Id><Name>Players</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To save his pregnant wife, an emergency room nurse unwillingly partners with an injured murder suspect in a race against time and renegade cops.</Description><Id>80221677</Id><Name>Point Blank</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An assassin on the verge of retirement must put the good life on hold when his greedy boss sends a squad of young, ruthless killers to take him out.</Description><Id>80223052</Id><Name>Polar</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>During a storm that wrecks his ship, super-strong sailor Popeye washes ashore and winds up rooming at the Oyl household, where he meets Olive.</Description><Id>60028294</Id><Name>Popeye</Name><ReleaseYear>1980</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A tidal wave spells disaster for a ship of New Year's Eve revelers when it capsizes the mammoth vessel, sending passengers into a battle for survival.</Description><Id>70044697</Id><Name>Poseidon</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Aspiring to fulfill his father’s dream and become a civil services officer, a young man loses his way upon becoming entangled with a criminal lynchpin.</Description><Id>81215481</Id><Name>Pranaam</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A thief commits the heist of his life, only to awaken the next morning with no memory. Now, he must race to find the missing loot.</Description><Id>70134539</Id><Name>Prince</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Suddenly possessed with supernatural powers, a father sets out to help his estranged daughter, who's at risk of losing everything she's lived for.</Description><Id>80226424</Id><Name>Psychokinesis</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A notorious terrorist manipulates an Indian army major's jilted lover into helping him obtain a classified military code.</Description><Id>60037397</Id><Name>Pukar</Name><ReleaseYear>2000</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Thom tells her grandson about his grandfather, a sailor who left 61 years ago to seek his fortune, and asks him to find out what happened to her spouse.</Description><Id>81020161</Id><Name>Pulang</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this remake of a 1996 Danish thriller, a drug pusher incurs his suppliers' wrath when he gets busted and is left without the money he owes.</Description><Id>70253590</Id><Name>Pusher</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The plot thickens around two horse-racing competitors when three beautiful women come into their lives and a murder is committed.</Description><Id>70096752</Id><Name>Race</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this sequel set in the world of horse racing, half-brothers Ranvir and Rajiv Singh return for another complex tale of love, greed and violence.</Description><Id>70229046</Id><Name>Race 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After street smart kid Raees rises to become Gujarat's bootlegging king in the 1980s, he tries to balance his life of crime with helping his people.</Description><Id>80164778</Id><Name>Raees</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>During World War II, a Chinese railroad worker leads a group of brave resistance fighters against the forces of Japanese occupation.</Description><Id>80138469</Id><Name>Railroad Tigers</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Lone-wolf vigilante Bill Williamson is back, taking aim at the U.S. government and eluding the pursuit of two FBI agents who are on his trail.</Description><Id>80038358</Id><Name>Rampage: President Down</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When Prince Lee Cheong returns to Joseon after his brother’s death, he finds the kingdom plagued by deadly creatures – but they’re not the only threat.</Description><Id>81034931</Id><Name>Rampant</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>During World War II, daredevil star Miss Julia entertains soldiers at the Indo-Burma border, where she's caught up in a web of love and deceit.</Description><Id>80176342</Id><Name>Rangoon</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A group of teenagers witnesses Soviet and Cuban paratroopers descending on their small Colorado town and systematically setting off World War III.</Description><Id>896678</Id><Name>Red Dawn</Name><ReleaseYear>1984</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Inside one of Cairo's most impoverished areas exists a place where criminals control everything and everyone.</Description><Id>81035845</Id><Name>Regatta</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two huge soccer fans must go on a rambunctious road trip to fix a big match between Malaysia and Thailand, or they'll draw the ire of a loan shark.</Description><Id>80163265</Id><Name>Rembat</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Following the written instructions of his friend, senile Zev crosses the country to find and murder the Nazi who killed their families in Auschwitz.</Description><Id>80022605</Id><Name>Remember</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Undead Apocalypse continues as super-soldier Alice finds her way to a supposed sanctuary in Los Angeles, which may just be a deadly trap.</Description><Id>70128695</Id><Name>Resident Evil: Afterlife</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When thugs prey upon innocent factory workers, a small-time scammer trains for revenge by studying the moves of Shaolin temple monks.</Description><Id>70130432</Id><Name>Return To The 36th Chamber</Name><ReleaseYear>1980</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In gritty 1980s New York, two Chinese immigrant boys rise through the ranks of the infamous Green Dragons gang, where they're trained to kill.</Description><Id>80017280</Id><Name>Revenge of the Green Dragons</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Hell-bent on avenging the murder of his family, a former detective infiltrates a remote island that serves as a prison for vicious death row criminals.</Description><Id>81000511</Id><Name>Revenger</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Following a devastating alien invasion, an American soldier and a French foreign aid worker attempt to find refuge in the Kenyan countryside.</Description><Id>80176592</Id><Name>Revolt</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Stranded at a summer camp when aliens attack the planet, four teens with nothing in common embark on a perilous mission to save the world.</Description><Id>80218306</Id><Name>Rim of the World</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Seeking vengeance for the murder of his wife, a cop robs a bank in order to be thrown into prison with the Russian kingpin who ruined his life.</Description><Id>80095807</Id><Name>Riot</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When the Sheriff of Nottingham takes his beloved captive, Robin Hood embarks on a daring rescue mission at the tyrant's castle.</Description><Id>81017593</Id><Name>Robin Hood: The Rebellion</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Sylvester Stallone shot to fame as Rocky Balboa, an unknown fighter who's given a shot at fighting world champ Apollo Creed as a publicity stunt.</Description><Id>915927</Id><Name>Rocky</Name><ReleaseYear>1976</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A reclusive pawn shop owner sets his sights on revenge when vicious gangsters kidnap his drug-addicted neighbor's young daughter.</Description><Id>80103428</Id><Name>Rocky Handsome</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this dystopian sequel, kills equal points in a violently gory annual cross-country road race sponsored by the United Corporations of America.</Description><Id>80152003</Id><Name>Roger Corman's Death Race 2050</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two common boys travel from India to Thailand to find success and money, enjoying their friendship and finding ways to cheat the cheats.</Description><Id>80032097</Id><Name>Romeo Ranjha</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A con man uncovers a deadly secret and must save his lady love, the little girl who insists she's his daughter and the small-town locals from the mob.</Description><Id>70229043</Id><Name>Rowdy Rathore</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An ex-MMA champion reduced to fixing fights in Mexico must win one last match to save his girlfriend, who's been kidnapped by the mob.</Description><Id>80192015</Id><Name>Rumble</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>During a visit to the Bronx to help out at his uncle's store, a cheerful martial arts expert springs into action when a gang terrorizes the shop.</Description><Id>923574</Id><Name>Rumble in the Bronx</Name><ReleaseYear>1995</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Siddharth falls in love with beautiful Jhanvi. But Jhanvi's brother Ganpat is overly possessive – and determined to destroy their relationship.</Description><Id>70001082</Id><Name>Run</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Anti-corruption investigator William Luk must join forces with detective Lau Po-keung to bring down a crime syndicate involved in sports betting.</Description><Id>80144152</Id><Name>S Storm</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a fictional megalopolis, a stunning underworld theft triggers a fierce power struggle among the gangsters, with an enigmatic cop on their trail.</Description><Id>81157385</Id><Name>Saaho</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Two close childhood friends take drastically different paths in life, but meet by chance years later and fall in love, unaware of their past bond.</Description><Id>80158479</Id><Name>Salaakhen</Name><ReleaseYear>1975</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Biblical story of Samson becomes this sword-and-sandals epic about an Israelite warrior whose God-given brawn is undone by a beautiful temptress.</Description><Id>80222301</Id><Name>Samson</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After the invasion of Iraq in 2003, a reluctant soldier's platoon is dispatched on a dangerous mission to repair a hostile village's water system.</Description><Id>80118916</Id><Name>Sand Castle</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A simple farmer's life becomes complicated after he resolves to save his village from an economic crisis by traveling to Australia to earn money.</Description><Id>80115858</Id><Name>Sardaarji 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A ruthless businessman’s mission to expose electoral fraud brings him into a heated and dangerous political conflict with two corrupt ministers.</Description><Id>81072516</Id><Name>Sarkar</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A ruthless businessman’s mission to expose electoral fraud brings him into a heated and dangerous political conflict with two corrupt ministers.</Description><Id>81075235</Id><Name>Sarkar</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A former professional boxer serving time in a brutal labor camp must fight incredible odds to gain his freedom and avenge an act of violence.</Description><Id>80156684</Id><Name>Savage Dog</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Scorpion King joins forces with a Nubian princess in an all-or-nothing fight to stop a warlord from claiming the souls of the vanquished.</Description><Id>80994444</Id><Name>Scorpion King 5: Book of Souls</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Dreamy delivery girl Ramona captures Scott Pilgrim's heart, but he must vanquish all seven of her evil exes in martial arts battles to win her love.</Description><Id>70117312</Id><Name>Scott Pilgrim vs. the World</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this dramatic recreation, U.S. Navy SEAL Team 6 trains for a critical mission, then executes a tough nighttime raid on Osama Bin Laden's compound.</Description><Id>70260512</Id><Name>Seal Team Six: The Raid on Osama Bin Laden</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A group of weary warriors transport a suspected witch believed to be responsible for spreading the devastating Black Plague.</Description><Id>70126573</Id><Name>Season of the Witch</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After taking a job as a mall security guard, a former Marine steps up to protect a young girl who's being hunted by heavily armed mercenaries.</Description><Id>80161921</Id><Name>Security</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An aspiring yet aimless actor takes over his ailing father's job as an ambulance driver, unwittingly getting involved in an organ-trafficking network.</Description><Id>81038046</Id><Name>Sei</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A diamond heist goes horribly wrong, and the group of friends who sought to make a fortune must instead fight for their very survival.</Description><Id>70199239</Id><Name>Set Up</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As three kingdoms struggle for control of a walled city, a figure with a rare power spins a web of intrigue that entangles a king's court.</Description><Id>81034600</Id><Name>Shadow</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When they're blackmailed after a hit-and-run, a troubled rich girl and her wild friends stage a fake kidnapping with a plan to collect the ransom.</Description><Id>80165855</Id><Name>Shaitan</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Robert Downey Jr. stars as the legendary sleuth Sherlock Holmes in this Guy Ritchie-helmed reinvention of Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's detective series.</Description><Id>70110558</Id><Name>Sherlock Holmes</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young man enrolls at a college and becomes a rival to the student-union president, who’s using force and intimidation to advance his criminal agenda.</Description><Id>70059284</Id><Name>Shiva</Name><ReleaseYear>1990</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Based on a true story, this action film follows an incident that stunned a nation in the early 1990s. In Mumbai, India, the notorious gangster Maya holds off veteran cop Khan and a force of more than 200 policemen in a six-hour bloody gunfight.</Description><Id>70073018</Id><Name>Shootout at Lokhandwala</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Unexpected wildlife adventures and valuable life lessons await seven city kids when they suddenly become lost in the forest during a school field trip.</Description><Id>81086640</Id><Name>Shortcut Safari</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a drug lord kidnaps his girlfriend’s daughter, a retired assassin leaves his newly peaceful life to go on a ruthless rampage to rescue the child.</Description><Id>81012943</Id><Name>Silencer</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In these intertwined tales, an ex-con avenges a hooker's death, a gumshoe gets mixed up with dangerous vixens, and a cop saves a dancer from a rapist.</Description><Id>70021630</Id><Name>Sin City</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As the result of a TV journalist's curiosity, the amazing saga of an honorable government tax collector's past comes to light.</Description><Id>70298393</Id><Name>Singh Saab the Great</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Nearly a century after artificial intelligence tried to eradicate people from Earth, two survivors search for a human enclave rumored to still exist.</Description><Id>80196584</Id><Name>Singularity</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A New Jersey detective whose family was killed by an international gangster teams up with a Bangkok cop on a quest to bring down a criminal empire.</Description><Id>80039602</Id><Name>Skin Trade</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To capture a crime lord who killed his partner and kidnapped his partner's daughter, a Hong Kong detective teams with a smart aleck American gambler.</Description><Id>80099089</Id><Name>Skiptrace</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The security chief at a top-level medical facility must fight to ensure that revolutionary cancer research doesn't fall into the wrong hands.</Description><Id>80156927</Id><Name>Sky on Fire</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a wild night of partying, Terry discovers that he's one of the few people left on Earth, then sets out to solve the mystery of what happened.</Description><Id>70141971</Id><Name>Skyline</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Determined to find the woman he loves, a Scottish teenager braves the Western frontier of 19th-century America, with bounty hunters hot on his trail.</Description><Id>80029901</Id><Name>Slow West</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When the Commando Elite, a group of toy action figures, are released before they've been tested, they attack the children playing with them.</Description><Id>20129240</Id><Name>Small Soldiers</Name><ReleaseYear>1998</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a mission to rescue a U.S. congressman from the Taliban ends with two men left behind, their sniper buddies go against orders to get them back.</Description><Id>80099306</Id><Name>Sniper: Special Ops</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Earth's remaining inhabitants are confined to a single train circling the globe as revolution brews among the class-divided cars.</Description><Id>70270364</Id><Name>Snowpiercer</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young Han Solo tries to settle an old score with the help of his new buddy Chewbacca, a crew of space smugglers and a cunning old friend.</Description><Id>80220814</Id><Name>Solo: A Star Wars Story</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young Han Solo tries to settle an old score with the help of his new buddy Chewbacca, a crew of space smugglers and a cunning old friend.</Description><Id>81046962</Id><Name>Solo: A Star Wars Story (Spanish Version)</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this epic tale, a once-murderous sea captain is holed up in a monastery in retreat from the devil, whom the captain fears is coming for his soul.</Description><Id>70120167</Id><Name>Solomon Kane</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young petty thief who received protection from a notorious inmate in jail is forced to spring his defender from prison and help pull off a heist.</Description><Id>80027378</Id><Name>Son of a Gun</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A retired engineer agrees to help NASA prevent a Russian satellite from falling to Earth if he and his over-the-hill pals can man the mission.</Description><Id>60001363</Id><Name>Space Cowboys</Name><ReleaseYear>2000</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When an otherworldly force wreaks havoc on a war-torn European city, an engineer teams up with an elite Special Ops unit to stop it.</Description><Id>80098200</Id><Name>Spectral</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The seemingly invincible Spider-Man goes up against an all-new crop of villains in the third installment of the blockbuster adventure series.</Description><Id>70047101</Id><Name>Spider-Man 3</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After being bitten by a radioactive spider, Brooklyn teen Miles Morales gets a crash course in web-slinging from his alternate-dimension counterparts.</Description><Id>81002747</Id><Name>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his girlfriend dumps him for being a bore, a working stiff discovers that his father is a secret agent and a dangerous thug is targeting them.</Description><Id>80093213</Id><Name>Spy Time</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When an Intelligence Bureau officer’s phone-tapping day job leads him to a serial killer, he must track down and thwart the murderer’s next steps.</Description><Id>81016194</Id><Name>Spyder</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After witnessing an assassin's slaughter, a young girl holes up in a farmhouse with a suicidal vet, who must use wits and guts to fend off the killer.</Description><Id>80065754</Id><Name>Standoff</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As the remnants of the Resistance flee Kylo Ren and the First Order, Rey seeks out Luke Skywalker – but he wants nothing more to do with the Force.</Description><Id>80192018</Id><Name>Star Wars: Episode VIII: The Last Jedi</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>New undercover cop partners Starsky and Hutch must overcome their differences to solve an important case with help from street informant Huggy Bear.</Description><Id>60033320</Id><Name>Starsky &amp; Hutch</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Amid a coup, a North Korean agent escapes south with the country's injured leader in an attempt to keep him alive and prevent a Korean war.</Description><Id>80226234</Id><Name>Steel Rain</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a tough upbringing, natural-born fighter José Aldo confronts his personal demons in his quest to become an MMA champion in this sports biopic.</Description><Id>80147513</Id><Name>Stronger Than the World</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a near-death trip home, a Marine looking to help his comrade survive returns to the underground world of MMA, where new battles await.</Description><Id>81152923</Id><Name>Submission</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To get away from the thug life, cocaine dealer Youngblood Priest puts together one last deal that will net him enough money to start over.</Description><Id>60033247</Id><Name>Superfly</Name><ReleaseYear>1972</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When she loses her city's vital power supply, Kryptonian Kara follows it to Earth in the hopes of retrieving it. Although gifted with powers like her cousin Superman, Kara struggles to defeat the evil Selena, who now controls the mighty object.</Description><Id>60001761</Id><Name>Supergirl</Name><ReleaseYear>1984</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this adaptation of the comic strip, Juan López must balance an office job with heroic feats to save the love of his life and native planet Chitón.</Description><Id>80202809</Id><Name>Superlopez</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When Superman returns to Metropolis, he finds that Lois Lane has moved on to another man and Lex Luthor is developing a new plan to rule the world.</Description><Id>70041963</Id><Name>Superman Returns</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Haunted by the past, a master swordsman masks his identity to work anonymously as a janitor in a brothel, setting in motion a violent chain of events.</Description><Id>80114989</Id><Name>Sword Master</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Shaolin warrior Tung Chien-chen is injured in battle against the hated Wu Tang clan, and nursed back to health by a knife-throwing master. As he recovers, Tung learns this deadly art, and also falls in love with his teacher's daughter.</Description><Id>70100527</Id><Name>Sword Masters: Two Champions of Shaolin</Name><ReleaseYear>1980</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Determined to get his mitts on $9 billion in a secret DEA account so he can fight terrorism, a rogue agent recruits an encryption expert to hack in.</Description><Id>60020745</Id><Name>Swordfish</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A motley crew of bank robbers plans their next heist after a former colleague convinces them to target an armored car carrying $20 million.</Description><Id>70117294</Id><Name>Takers</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A man and a woman on the run from the law are drawn to each other through the common bond of their mutual dependency.</Description><Id>80202090</Id><Name>Tamanchey</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Doubting her future as a nun, a woman attempts to have a child, triggering a mystic tribal prophecy that could force her to make a godly sacrifice.</Description><Id>81172909</Id><Name>Tatu</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A Navy SEAL is sent to a war-torn African jungle to rescue a doctor, only to realize he must also save the refugees in the physician's care.</Description><Id>60026139</Id><Name>Tears of the Sun</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A gangster hires goon Teefa to abduct his friend’s daughter for an arranged marriage, but things get tricky when Teefa develops feelings for the girl.</Description><Id>81036338</Id><Name>Teefa in Trouble</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After exposure to a strange, glowing ooze, four mutant turtles train as ninjas in the sewers and fight crime wherever they find it.</Description><Id>1029730</Id><Name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Movie</Name><ReleaseYear>1990</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Ten years after John Connor saved Earth from Judgment Day, he encounters T-X, a robotic assassin ordered to finish what T-1000 started.</Description><Id>60029154</Id><Name>Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>All grown up in post-apocalyptic 2018, John Connor must lead the resistance of humans against increasingly dominating militaristic robots.</Description><Id>70103524</Id><Name>Terminator Salvation</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This high-octane thriller tells the story of a man on a mission to reclaim what was taken from him and the agent who's determined to stop him.</Description><Id>70236586</Id><Name>Tezz</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In London, a mysterious blind man named Kenny appears to be an assassin who uses echolocation to kill, but there is more to Kenny than meets the eye.</Description><Id>70229048</Id><Name>Thaandavam</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a violent prison in 1970s Mexico, a young inmate lands a spot on a football team that doubles as an enforcer squad for a corrupt administration.</Description><Id>80161104</Id><Name>The 4th Company</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Nursing a broken heart, an IT specialist moves to London to audition for a reality TV show that unexpectedly turns into a real-life cartel drama.</Description><Id>81172908</Id><Name>The Accidental Spy</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Formerly a Korean resistance fighter, a policeman working for Japan is tasked with tracking down resistance leaders before they acquire explosives.</Description><Id>80139199</Id><Name>The Age of Shadows</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Now a celebrity, Benjie is tasked with taking care of a General's young son, who has information about a looming terrorist threat.</Description><Id>81010863</Id><Name>The Amazing Praybeyt Benjamin</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Crunch Calhoun, a daredevil motorcyclist and mostly reformed con artist, agrees to do one last job: helping his brother Nicky steal a priceless book.</Description><Id>70253594</Id><Name>The Art of the Steal</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While working at a family friend's business, a penniless orphan draws the attention of a corrupt competitor and is torn between divided loyalties.</Description><Id>80997857</Id><Name>The Bare-Footed Kid</Name><ReleaseYear>1993</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Feeling guilty after a high-speed chase leaves a girl dead, a determined sergeant pursues the crime boss who triggered the fatal car accident.</Description><Id>70117354</Id><Name>The Beast Stalker</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As a killer stalks the streets, a troubled young courier suspects that a doctor may be the long-lost sister he hasn't seen since childhood.</Description><Id>80174727</Id><Name>The Bittersweet</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Determined to protect a sacred text that promises to save humanity, Eli goes on a quest westward across the barren, postapocalyptic country.</Description><Id>70114342</Id><Name>The Book of Eli</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Bounty hunter Milo Boyd finds his latest assignment downright satisfying as he learns that the bail-jumper he must chase down is his ex-wife, Nicole.</Description><Id>70128696</Id><Name>The Bounty Hunter</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>With entry into the European Union at stake, Albania must rely on a mash-up of elite cops to take down a slippery drug lord dominating its economy.</Description><Id>81127333</Id><Name>The Brave</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Brothers Jake and Will Grimm travel from village to village, posing as exterminators of magical creatures. But in reality, they're expert con artists.</Description><Id>70021661</Id><Name>The Brothers Grimm</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After losing everything, a young man rebuilds his life and finds love in 1920s Shanghai – all while rising to power in an organized crime syndicate.</Description><Id>80997866</Id><Name>The Bund</Name><ReleaseYear>1983</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A special operations officer vows to get revenge against the terrorist who killed his friend in a brutal attack.</Description><Id>81035883</Id><Name>The Cell</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A young Senegalese-French man from humble roots sets out to climb Mount Everest to impress the woman he loves – and slowly becomes a media sensation.</Description><Id>80194671</Id><Name>The Climb</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Orbiting above a planet on the brink of war, scientists test a device to solve an energy crisis and end up face-to-face with a dark alternate reality.</Description><Id>80134431</Id><Name>The Cloverfield Paradox</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After an unexpected misstep, a crew of skilled Parisian robbers find themselves forced to carry out a daring heist for a powerful crime organization.</Description><Id>80196044</Id><Name>The Crew</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>One year after Eric Draven and his fiancée are murdered, Draven – watched over by a hypnotic crow – returns from the grave to exact revenge.</Description><Id>408911</Id><Name>The Crow</Name><ReleaseYear>1994</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An aspiring filmmaker records the chaos of an alien invasion while struggling to stay alive with her sister and a bickering band of survivors.</Description><Id>80231601</Id><Name>The Darkest Dawn</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A broke martial arts instructor takes a side gig with a mobster, who pairs him with a veteran thug for a weekend of fisticuffs-fueled debt collection.</Description><Id>80198585</Id><Name>The Debt Collector</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The life of a bank manager is turned upside down when a friend from his past manipulates him into faking his own death and taking off on an adventure.</Description><Id>80063265</Id><Name>The Do-Over</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Duke boys are back in this comedy based on the TV series, following Bo and Luke as they tear around Hazzard County in their trusty Dodge Charger.</Description><Id>70021652</Id><Name>The Dukes of Hazzard</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The mischievous Duke boys, Bo and Luke, are sent to live with their Uncle Jesse and cousin Daisy in this prequel movie to the popular TV series.</Description><Id>70061763</Id><Name>The Dukes of Hazzard: The Beginning</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Seele orders an all-out attack on NERV, aiming to destroy the Evas before Gendo can trigger Third Impact and Instrumentality under his control.</Description><Id>60024788</Id><Name>The End of Evangelion</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A dying kung fu master sends his last student to track down five former pupils in order to learn which one of them has become evil.</Description><Id>60001377</Id><Name>The Five Venoms</Name><ReleaseYear>1978</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In Qing-dynasty China, the emperor commands that a weapon be invented to kill at a distance without a trace. Then he orders it used on its wielders.</Description><Id>80999107</Id><Name>The Flying Guillotine</Name><ReleaseYear>1975</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Jackie Chan and Jet Li star in this rousing adventure about a martial arts movie fan who finds a mystical staff that transports him to ancient China.</Description><Id>70084795</Id><Name>The Forbidden Kingdom</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As the Japanese invasion looms, Chinese kung fu master Ip Man's world changes when rival master Gong Er and her father arrive in his village.</Description><Id>70270775</Id><Name>The Grandmaster</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In seventh-century Korea, the commander of Ansi Fortress, Yang Man-chun, combats Tang invaders in a retelling of an epic clash against all odds.</Description><Id>81031306</Id><Name>The Great Battle</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After unwittingly using his skills to obtain military secrets, a gambler is pursued by a police officer who happens to be his doppelgänger.</Description><Id>81213898</Id><Name>The Great Gambler</Name><ReleaseYear>1979</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In 1920s Beijing, a host of talented performers gather to show off their skills. The challenge: reproduce a magic trick called the Eight Immortals.</Description><Id>70242536</Id><Name>The Great Magician</Name><ReleaseYear>2011</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In World War II, a battalion goes on a daring rescue mission to liberate the Americans and Filipinos who've been captured by the Japanese.</Description><Id>60033312</Id><Name>The Great Raid</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After learning his brother died on a mission in Romania, a former soldier teams up with two allies to hunt down a mysterious enemy and exact revenge.</Description><Id>80200961</Id><Name>The Hard Way</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Years after the Civil War, a bounty hunter and his captive are waylaid by a Wyoming blizzard and hole up in a way station with six dicey strangers.</Description><Id>80064515</Id><Name>The Hateful Eight</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>New straight-arrow sheriff Wallace finds he must join forces with brutal ex-lawman Leland to protect a troubled border town from a cartel hit man.</Description><Id>80100260</Id><Name>The Hollow Point</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a dystopian, near-future United States, a deportation caseworker who has begun to question authority tries to safeguard a woman and her young son.</Description><Id>80218939</Id><Name>The Humanity Bureau</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A deadly hurricane with mile-high waves provides the perfect cover for stealing $600 million from a U.S. Treasury outpost in Mississippi.</Description><Id>80215923</Id><Name>The Hurricane Heist</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a deal with the devil comes due, the immortal Doctor Parnassus must renegotiate the pact to save his daughter and right the wrongs of his past.</Description><Id>70113532</Id><Name>The Imaginarium of Doctor Parnassus</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Daredevil secret agent and father of the groom Steve gives conservative podiatrist and father of the bride Jerry prenuptial jitters when they meet.</Description><Id>60027701</Id><Name>The In-Laws</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In lawless badlands, reclusive Cabeleira sets out to discover the fate of his gunman father and grows to be a feared assassin himself.</Description><Id>80127990</Id><Name>The Killer</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Private eye Joe Hallenbeck is forced to team up with a disgraced quarterback to uncover a conspiracy by a politician and a football team owner.</Description><Id>684847</Id><Name>The Last Boy Scout</Name><ReleaseYear>1991</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An ex-colonel forms a special paramilitary group focused on combatting drug trafficking on the Paraguayan border.</Description><Id>81055395</Id><Name>The Last Runway</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A star of hunting videos strives to bond with his 12-year-old son on a wilderness trip but learns familial connections can't be forced.</Description><Id>80176715</Id><Name>The Legacy of a Whitetail Deer Hunter</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Aragorn is revealed as the heir to the ancient kings as he, Gandalf and the other members of the broken fellowship struggle to save Gondor.</Description><Id>60004484</Id><Name>The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Frodo and Sam head to Mordor to destroy the One Ring of Power while Gimli, Legolas and Aragorn search for the orc-captured Merry and Pippin.</Description><Id>60004483</Id><Name>The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A magical ring holds the key to life, death and love for a marine archaeologist who seems to live two lives in different centuries and countries.</Description><Id>80038446</Id><Name>The Lovers</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Leveraging his ability to withstand pain, a young man trains to follow in the footsteps of his martial-arts hero in this high-action, meta comedy.</Description><Id>81057229</Id><Name>The Man Who Feels No Pain</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An aging Zorro passes the torch to a young successor, schooling him in discipline and training him to take up the sword against crooked officials.</Description><Id>5670479</Id><Name>The Mask of Zorro</Name><ReleaseYear>1998</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A computer hacker learns that what most people perceive as reality is actually a simulation created by machines, and joins a rebellion to break free.</Description><Id>20557937</Id><Name>The Matrix</Name><ReleaseYear>1999</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The crew must protect Zion, the last outpost still under human control, after it is pinpointed by the machines responsible for the Matrix.</Description><Id>60027695</Id><Name>The Matrix Reloaded</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The final installment in the Matrix trilogy finds an unconscious Neo trapped in a subway station in a zone between the Matrix and the machine world.</Description><Id>60031303</Id><Name>The Matrix Revolutions</Name><ReleaseYear>2003</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After sparing a girl's life during a massacre, an elite Triad assassin is targeted by an onslaught of murderous gangsters.</Description><Id>80148162</Id><Name>The Night Comes for Us</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The ordered life of a Reykjavik heart surgeon unravels when his daughter descends into a life of drugs and crime thanks to a sinister boyfriend.</Description><Id>80156405</Id><Name>The Oath</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After witnessing a murder, Simon Garden is framed – and the only evidence that proves his innocence is a videotape locked inside a bank vault.</Description><Id>60022962</Id><Name>The Parole Officer</Name><ReleaseYear>2001</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After terrorists trigger a nuclear blast in Russia, a U.S. Special Forces intelligence agent and a nuclear weapons expert come to the rescue.</Description><Id>20159719</Id><Name>The Peacemaker</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A medical apprentice in 11th-century Persia disguises himself as a Jew to study at a school that does not admit Christians.</Description><Id>80014996</Id><Name>The Physician</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A former Mafia hit man living quietly as a mechanic veers back into his old world after his daughter is abducted and faces an old foe in New Orleans.</Description><Id>80013712</Id><Name>The Prince</Name><ReleaseYear>2014</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A cop-turned-convict discovers a crime syndicate inside a prison lorded over by an inmate crime boss – and joins in on their nightly heists.</Description><Id>80177865</Id><Name>The Prison</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his outlaw dad is kidnapped, Tommy “White Knife” Stockburn sets off across the West on a rescue mission with five brothers he never knew he had.</Description><Id>80039517</Id><Name>The Ridiculous 6</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A turbulent vacation turns deadly when a fugitive and his crew kidnap a river rafting guide and her family, forcing them down the dangerous river.</Description><Id>17672040</Id><Name>The River Wild</Name><ReleaseYear>1994</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Hired by a Russian politician to steal the formula for cold fusion, master thief Simon Templar falls for the scientist who has unlocked the secret.</Description><Id>1153194</Id><Name>The Saint</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Master thief Simon Templar – also known as the Saint – is hired by a wealthy banker to find his kidnapped daughter, but not all is as it seems.</Description><Id>80160346</Id><Name>The Saint</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The Seven Deadly Sins aid the Sky People against a powerful group of demons hellbent on resurrecting a demonic beast sealed over 3,000 years ago.</Description><Id>81006261</Id><Name>The Seven Deadly Sins the Movie: Prisoners of the Sky</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Besieged by overwhelming enemy forces, Irish soldiers on a U.N. peacekeeping mission in Africa valiantly defend their outpost in this true story.</Description><Id>80041653</Id><Name>The Siege of Jadotville</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After years of limited contact with Earth, an inquisitive teen who lives on Mars makes an interplanetary trek to discover his own origins.</Description><Id>80097424</Id><Name>The Space Between Us</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Following his best friend's death, Arci takes charge of her two boisterous children with some help from their gang-affiliated uncle.</Description><Id>80162503</Id><Name>The Super Parental Guardians</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a group of hijackers takes passengers aboard a subway train hostage and demand a ransom, it's up to dispatcher Walter Garber to bring them down.</Description><Id>70112730</Id><Name>The Taking of Pelham 123</Name><ReleaseYear>2009</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Based on the H.G. Wells classic, this adventure follows a scientist and inventor who's determined to prove to doubters that time travel is possible.</Description><Id>60022645</Id><Name>The Time Machine</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An American tourist seeking solace for his shattered heart instead finds it in danger again after encountering a beautiful Interpol agent.</Description><Id>70142888</Id><Name>The Tourist</Name><ReleaseYear>2010</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After a government spy is hospitalized, New York City cab driver Jimmy unwillingly takes over the spy's role – with the aid of a computerized tuxedo.</Description><Id>60022980</Id><Name>The Tuxedo</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An empress rules over a land where men are subservient to women. But a prophecy reveals that a boy will become king and restore the male regime.</Description><Id>70025372</Id><Name>The Twins Effect II</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After losing her eyesight in an accident, a woman lands in a love triangle as she looks for meaning in her life.</Description><Id>81035846</Id><Name>The Walls of the Moon</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Greed, revenge, world domination: It's all in a day's work for James Bond, who's on a mission to protect an oil heiress from a notorious terrorist.</Description><Id>28371873</Id><Name>The World Is Not Enough</Name><ReleaseYear>1999</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To escape his life of crime, a Paris drug dealer takes on one last job involving Spain, unhinged gangsters, his longtime crush and his scheming mother.</Description><Id>81021528</Id><Name>The World Is Yours</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To avenge his master, a wine-loving young man steps up his fighting skills to defeat a powerful thief in a life-or-death match.</Description><Id>80997861</Id><Name>The Young Vagabond</Name><ReleaseYear>1985</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After losing a boxing match, a talented Muay Thai fighter leaves home to train with the best. On his quest, he finds friends, foes and lots of action.</Description><Id>80224233</Id><Name>Thong Dee Fun Khao</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To save Asgard from a bloodthirsty goddess of death, the mighty Thor will have to battle his way to freedom and find a way back home.</Description><Id>80186608</Id><Name>Thor: Ragnarok</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A master criminal engineers his own shooting during a police raid, then refuses treatment while awaiting rescue in a tense standoff at a hospital.</Description><Id>80117455</Id><Name>Three</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Imprisoned for drug smuggling as a child, a young man uses the law he studied while in jail to take revenge on those who wronged him.</Description><Id>80141767</Id><Name>Tiger</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>While searching for their missing archaeology professor, a group of students discovers a cave where time passes differently than it does on the surface.</Description><Id>81023636</Id><Name>Time Trap</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Pierce Brosnan stars in this 007 installment, which teams the secret agent and a sexy Chinese superspy against a megalomaniacal media mogul.</Description><Id>17016471</Id><Name>Tomorrow Never Dies</Name><ReleaseYear>1997</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a bike messenger falls into debt with organized criminals, a sexy woman draws him into her high-stakes world of parkour, teaching him new skills.</Description><Id>70295176</Id><Name>Tracers</Name><ReleaseYear>2015</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>As a zombie outbreak sweeps the country, a dad and his daughter take a harrowing train journey in an attempt to reach the only city that's still safe.</Description><Id>80117824</Id><Name>Train to Busan</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The subterranean, worm-like creatures are back, and Graboid-hunter Burt Gummer suspects they've been weaponized.</Description><Id>80233493</Id><Name>Tremors 6: A Cold Day in Hell</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After being framed, a policewoman languishing in prison hopes that her three sons will deliver justice and restore her honor.</Description><Id>20717860</Id><Name>Trimurti</Name><ReleaseYear>1995</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Loyalties are tested when five former special forces operatives reunite to steal a drug lord's fortune, unleashing a chain of unintended consequences.</Description><Id>80192187</Id><Name>Triple Frontier</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A crew of ruthless criminals hired to kill an influential heiress meet their match in a trio of surprisingly adept fighters who come to her aid.</Description><Id>80195901</Id><Name>Triple Threat</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The love-struck Prince Paris of Troy kidnaps beauty Helen from her husband, setting the two nations on a collision course for war.</Description><Id>60034571</Id><Name>Troy</Name><ReleaseYear>2004</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Starting with the Trojan Horse attack, this modest re-telling of Homer's epic covers well-known highlights of Odysseus's long journey home.</Description><Id>80017535</Id><Name>Troy: The Odyssey</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After his publisher markets his crime novel as a memoir, a novice author finds himself forcibly recruited into a deadly political plot in Venezuela.</Description><Id>80091658</Id><Name>True Memoirs of an International Assassin</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To retrieve a healing bead stolen from its guardian monks, a pair of bickering twin sisters face off against an entire gang of rival twins.</Description><Id>70123160</Id><Name>Twins Mission</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Six fearless surfers travel to the north coast of Iceland to ride waves unlike anything they've ever experienced, captured with high-tech cameras.</Description><Id>80216662</Id><Name>Under an Arctic Sky</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Jake's date with his dream girl takes a turn when she disappears, and Jake's grandpa – a former intelligence officer – sets out to find her.</Description><Id>80179288</Id><Name>Undercover Grandpa</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>To evade greedy pharmaceutical crooks, a medical scientist disguises himself as a struggling salesman to protect his groundbreaking cancer research.</Description><Id>81065786</Id><Name>Used Goods</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>After becoming stranded in the Philippine Sea during World War II, a tenacious Navy crew faces a dire lack of supplies and a string of shark attacks.</Description><Id>80108976</Id><Name>USS Indianapolis: Men of Courage</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A masked freedom fighter known as "V" takes up arms against a totalitarian government and finds an unlikely ally in a young woman.</Description><Id>70039175</Id><Name>V for Vendetta</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Moments after he arrives in Spain for an antiterrorism summit, U.S. President Ashton is shot.</Description><Id>70060005</Id><Name>Vantage Point</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A police official assembles an elaborate network of spies and undercover operatives to bring down a ruthless bandit with a private army.</Description><Id>80201822</Id><Name>Veerappan</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>This powerful Tamil action film follows the shared fate of two very different siblings: policeman Thiru and his roguish brother, Guru.</Description><Id>70225597</Id><Name>Vettai</Name><ReleaseYear>2012</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Framed for her father’s murder, an exiled Viking princess is guided by the god Odin as she prepares to return to her kingdom and reclaim the throne.</Description><Id>80219974</Id><Name>Viking Destiny</Name><ReleaseYear>2018</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When Pakistani authorities learn of a looming terrorist strike, they ask a retired intelligence officer to counter the attack before it's too late.</Description><Id>80187467</Id><Name>Waar</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a modern adaptation of a mythological tale, a devoted wife is willing to do whatever it takes to rescue her husband from the clutches of death.</Description><Id>80203780</Id><Name>Waarrior Savitri</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When his partner is killed and all clues point to a notorious assassin, FBI agent Jack Crawford sets out for revenge in this taut action-thriller.</Description><Id>70061480</Id><Name>War</Name><ReleaseYear>2007</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Terry and Bob excel at blackmailing small-time crooks. But when the two cops target a big score, they learn not all criminals are easily intimidated.</Description><Id>80103374</Id><Name>War on Everyone</Name><ReleaseYear>2016</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Raised in a boxing gym, two orphaned brothers become highly skilled martial artists and must combat threats in the streets and the ring.</Description><Id>81068732</Id><Name>We Are Legends</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In a future with a strict one-child policy, six septuplets must avoid government detection while searching for their missing sister.</Description><Id>80146805</Id><Name>What Happened to Monday</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>The getaway driver in a botched robbery puts his skills and smarts to the test when he receives shocking orders from an unknown caller.</Description><Id>80113669</Id><Name>Wheelman</Name><ReleaseYear>2017</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Paul Newman proves he's still got prodigious acting chops, playing an aging bank robber who may have one last job in him. Faking a stroke, the incarcerated Newman is transferred to a nursing home and the care of a skeptical nurse.</Description><Id>60000878</Id><Name>Where the Money Is</Name><ReleaseYear>2000</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Armed with an ingenious arsenal, two top-notch government agents are tasked with tracking down a diabolical scientist in this futuristic Western.</Description><Id>22007250</Id><Name>Wild Wild West</Name><ReleaseYear>1999</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>When a major drug deal goes sour, the queen of the Warsaw underworld must contend with a rival criminal, a crossed ally and a religious fighter.</Description><Id>81221851</Id><Name>Women of Mafia 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2019</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Working under treacherous conditions, an army of dedicated rescuers struggles to find anyone who survived the World Trade Center's tragic collapse.</Description><Id>70044693</Id><Name>World Trade Center</Name><ReleaseYear>2006</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Legendary lawman Wyatt Earp is continually at odds with a gang of renegade cowboys, culminating in a fiery showdown with the outlaws at the OK Corral.</Description><Id>60011597</Id><Name>Wyatt Earp</Name><ReleaseYear>1994</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>A notorious underground rush-seeker deemed untouchable by the law is coerced into cooperating with the government to infiltrate a Russian crime ring.</Description><Id>60023619</Id><Name>XXx</Name><ReleaseYear>2002</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>In this action-packed follow-up to XXX, U.S. intelligence officer Augustus Gibbons must thwart a massive conspiracy to overthrow the government.</Description><Id>70023960</Id><Name>XXX: State of the Union</Name><ReleaseYear>2005</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Up to his old tricks, con man Dharam poses as a millionaire to get his younger son married to the daughter of a wealthy businessman.</Description><Id>70308135</Id><Name>Yamla Pagla Deewana 2</Name><ReleaseYear>2013</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>An Israeli counterterrorism soldier with a secretly fabulous ambition to become a Manhattan hairstylist will do anything to make his dreams come true.</Description><Id>70087541</Id><Name>You Don't Mess with the Zohan</Name><ReleaseYear>2008</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary><DTO_TitleSummary><Description>Aided only by a tough female police officer, a Hong Kong taxi driver tries to escape from gangsters pursuing incriminating evidence left in his cab.</Description><Id>1145882</Id><Name>Young Tiger</Name><ReleaseYear>1973</ReleaseYear><TypeName>Movie</TypeName></DTO_TitleSummary></Titles></DTO_Category>